<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>blog on VoxDash</title><link>/categories/blog/</link><description>Recent content in blog on VoxDash</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/categories/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Frank Iero and The Patience Release New Song From Upcoming Album, 'Parachutes'</title><link>/frank-iero-patience-release-new-song-upcoming-album-parachutes.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/frank-iero-patience-release-new-song-upcoming-album-parachutes.html</guid><description>Frank Iero and The Patience have released their new song, “I’m A Mess” from their upcoming album, Parachutes.
The complete track list:
World Destroyer Veins! Veins!! Veins!!! I’m A Mess They Wanted Darkness… I’ll Let You Down Remedy Dear Percocet, I Don’t Think We Should See Each Other Anymore. Miss Me Oceans The Resurrectionist, or An Existential Crisis in C# Viva Indifference 9-6-15 Parachutes will be available for purchase on October 28.</description></item><item><title>Drew Barrymore on her &amp;quot;quiet, confident journey&amp;quot; to sobriety</title><link>/drew-barrymore-on-her-quiet-confident-journey-to-sobriety.html</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/drew-barrymore-on-her-quiet-confident-journey-to-sobriety.html</guid><description>Drew Barrymore said she has not had a drink for over two years after coming to the realization that drinking no longer served her or her life.&amp;nbsp;
“When you are stuck in a pattern or if you are going through things and you not only admit them out loud, but you force yourself to say, ‘I’m willing to make big changes,’ I think we all think we’re very weak when we don’t make those changes,” Barrymore told “CBS Mornings” co-host Gayle King.</description></item><item><title>Jessica Sterling - Net Worth, Age, Height, Birthday, Bio, Wiki!</title><link>/jesica-sterling.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/jesica-sterling.html</guid><description>Explore Jessica Sterling net worth, age, height, bio, birthday, wiki, and salary! Fashion model, and the wife of soccer goalie&amp;nbsp;Model and wife of soccer goalkeeper David Ospina. She has been featured in Daily Mail and The Sun. She has gained over 600,000 followers on Instagram..&amp;nbsp;She has been included by the Daily Mail and The Sun.&amp;nbsp;She has grown to more than 600,000. followers via Instagram. In this article, we will discover how old is Jessica Sterling?</description></item><item><title>Extra-wide shoe spec NYT Crossword Clue Answer 4 letters</title><link>/extra-wide-shoe-spec-nyt-crossword-clue-answer-4-letters-1250375.html</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/extra-wide-shoe-spec-nyt-crossword-clue-answer-4-letters-1250375.html</guid><description>Extra-wide shoe spec NYT Crossword Clue that we have found 1 exact answer, EEEE is the Answer for Extra-wide shoe spec NYT Crossword. It will help you solve today's New York Times Crossword Puzzles. by Sangeetha M | Updated Nov 25, 2023
Source: fresherslive
Extra-wide shoe spec NYT Crossword ClueThe Extra-wide shoe spec NYT crossword clue is a common type of clue that appears in The New York Times crossword puzzle.</description></item><item><title>Universal Makeup palette choices Crossword Clue</title><link>/universal-makeup-palette-choices-crossword-clue-1233117.html</link><pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/universal-makeup-palette-choices-crossword-clue-1233117.html</guid><description>We have 1 Possible solution with 5 letters for Makeup palette choices Crossword Clue Universal and the Answer is TONES for the clue of Makeup palette choices Universal Crossword Puzzle. Article continues below advertisement
Article continues below advertisement
Makeup palette choices CrosswordCheck Makeup palette choices Crossword Clue here, Universal will publish daily crosswords for the day. Players who are stuck with the Makeup palette choices Crossword Clue can head into this page to know the correct answer.</description></item><item><title>She Did the Harlem Shake Just Like Bow Wow: Bow Wows Daughter Dances with Mom and Has Fans</title><link>/she-did-the-harlem-shake-just-like-bow-wow-bow-wows-daughter-dances-with-mom-and-has-fans-seeing-double.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/she-did-the-harlem-shake-just-like-bow-wow-bow-wows-daughter-dances-with-mom-and-has-fans-seeing-double.html</guid><description>Shai Moss may get her dancing skills from her mom, Joie Chavis, but her father, Bow Wow, has been credited with giving her her looks.
On Sunday, June 20, Chavis uploaded another mommy-daughter dance video. The two recreated a viral TikTok video from TikTok user Kyle You Made That’s remix of @cheerlebridee’s “Poof Be Gone” song. Shai lip-synched over the video as it counted “5-6-7-8.” Then her mother joined in, and together they took on the quick challenge.</description></item><item><title>Anna Hall Wiki; Boyfriend, Parents, Height, Bio, Family, Age, Facts</title><link>/anna-hall-parents-wiki-boyfriend-height.html</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/anna-hall-parents-wiki-boyfriend-height.html</guid><description>Published Date: 25 Jan, 2023 Updated date: 25 Jan, 2023 By Phil Anna Hall is on cloud nine when it comes to her relationship life. She is dating an American young tennis player boyfriend for more than one year now. Her partner just faced defeat in the quarterfinal round of the ongoing Australian Open 2023. Who are Anna Hall parents? In this article, you can learn about Anna Hall wiki, age, height, father, bio, family, boyfriend, net worth, and other interesting facts.</description></item><item><title>Athena Calderone (Blogger) - Et, compleanno, biografia, fatti, famiglia, patrimonio netto, altezza</title><link>/athena-calderone-19741114-html.html</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/athena-calderone-19741114-html.html</guid><description>Blogger Athena Calderone est né le 14 Novembre, 1974 à United States (Ora ha 49 anni).
Fashion, lifestyle e food blogger che ha aperto il suo blog Instagram e Eyewoon per mostrare il suo lavoro di interior design e per avvicinarsi alla bellezza e alla prelibatezza di tutti i giorni.
All information about Athena Calderone can be found in this post. It will clarify Athena Calderone's info: biography, age, facts, income, family, wife &amp;amp; breakup of Athena Calderone.</description></item><item><title>Yiyi Sanchez: Musician, Age, Family, Relationship, Kids, Career, and Net Worth</title><link>/yiyi-sanchez.html</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/yiyi-sanchez.html</guid><description>Yiyi Sanchez is a notable musician. Music has been a huge part of Yisell Sanchez, aka Yiyi, since she grew up in Havana, Cuba. Like her sister before her, Yiyi found her way to music through the study of percussion. She began her musical journey by enrolling in classes at the Fernando Carnicer Conservatory. So, now let’s discuss Yiyi Sanchez’s life and net worth.
Yiyi Sanchez Early Life: Full Real Name Yiyi Sanchez Family Name Sanchez Profession Musician Date Of Birth January 1st, 1998 Age 25 Birthday January 1st Year Of Birth 1998 Nick Name Yiyi Current Residence N/A Country cuba Nationality NA Ethnicity N/A Religion N/A Yiyi was born in Havana, Cuba, on 1 January 1998.</description></item><item><title>Bono Leaves $150 Tip for Reuben Sandwich at Canter's Deli in L.A.</title><link>/us-bono-leaves-150-dollar-tip-for-reuben-sandwich-at-canters-deli-in-la-201536.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/us-bono-leaves-150-dollar-tip-for-reuben-sandwich-at-canters-deli-in-la-201536.html</guid><description>When Bono's hungry at 3 a.m., he does what many others up at that hour do: hit the local 24/7 deli or diner for grub. After U2's May 28 show at Los Angeles venue The Roxy, the 54-year-old rocker headed to the famed L.A. deli Canter's and asked a veteran server to choose his meal.
According to Billboard, the waitress brought Bono a Reuben sandwich, french fries, and onion rings. For dessert, the rocker enjoyed chocolate rugelach.</description></item><item><title>My Life Was Changed: Snoop Dogg Says Acquittal In Murder Trial Prompted Him to Stop Writing Ab</title><link>/my-life-was-changed-snoop-dogg-says-acquittal-in-murder-trial-prompted-him-to-stop-writing-about-death-and-violence.html</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/my-life-was-changed-snoop-dogg-says-acquittal-in-murder-trial-prompted-him-to-stop-writing-about-death-and-violence.html</guid><description>Snoop Dogg’s ascendance to fame transpired in the era of gangsta rap, and its brazen embrace of a life enmeshed in drugs, violence, and death. A willing proponent of the lifestyle, Snoop Dogg had his own successful gangsta persona that paid off for him in dividends, contributing to his commercially successful music career.
However, street life began to catch up with Snoop, and in 1996, he faced murder charges for his involvement in the shooting of a gang member in 1993, as recounted by The Los Angeles Times.</description></item><item><title>2 killed, 2 injured in I-90 Hoffman Estates crash involving deer</title><link>/2-killed-2-injured-in-i-90-hoffman-estates-crash-involving-deer.html</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/2-killed-2-injured-in-i-90-hoffman-estates-crash-involving-deer.html</guid><description>HOFFMAN ESTATES, Ill. (WLS) — Two people were killed in a two-vehicle crash involving a deer on I-90 in Hoffman Estates Monday morning, Illinois State Police said. One vehicle was traveling westbound on I-90 near milepost 59 at about 1:45 a.m. when it hit a deer and began to slow down as it headed to the right shoulder. The front end of a second vehicle hit the rear of the first vehicle and then overturned.</description></item><item><title>Army Veteran Kindly Myers In See-Through Silver Dress Is Holiday Ready</title><link>/army-veteran-kindly-myers-in-see-through-silver-dress-is-holiday-ready.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/army-veteran-kindly-myers-in-see-through-silver-dress-is-holiday-ready.html</guid><description>Model Kindly Myers is getting ready to celebrate the holiday season in style!
The Army National Reserve veteran donned a sparkling silver dress with sheer elements and see-through panels to remind her followers that she looks gorgeous in just about anything!
Kindly Myers Is Ready For Christmas In A See-Through Silver Dress In a post captioned “All that glitters is not gold,” the Playboy cover model looked like she walked straight out of the cover of a magazine as she stretched out on her stomach in a shimmering silver dress.</description></item><item><title>Janet Sheen Net Worth, Age, Height, Bio, Birthday, Wiki!</title><link>/janet-sheen.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/janet-sheen.html</guid><description>Explore Janet Sheen net worth, age, height, bio, birthday, wiki, and salary! In this article, we will discover how old is Janet Sheen? Who is Janet Sheen dating now &amp;amp; how much money does Janet Sheen have? Janet Sheen Biography Janet Sheen is one of the most popular and richest Film Producer who was born on July 8, 1944 in Dayton, Ohio, United States. Name Janet Sheen First Name Russ Last Name Snyder Occupation Film Producer Birthday July 8 Birth Year 1944 Place of Birth Dayton Home Town Ohio Birth Country United States Birth Sign Leo Full/Birth Name Father Not Available Mother Not Available Siblings Not Available Spouse Martin Sheen Children(s) Renée Estevez, Ramon Estevez, Charlie Sheen, Emilio Estevez Ethnicity, religion &amp;amp; political views Many peoples want to know what is Janet Sheen ethnicity, nationality, Ancestry &amp;amp; Race?</description></item><item><title>Memorial Day services across Northeast Florida remember fallen service members</title><link>/memorial-day-services-across-northeast-florida-remember-fallen-service-members.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/memorial-day-services-across-northeast-florida-remember-fallen-service-members.html</guid><description>JACKSONVILLE, Fla. – People came together Monday at Memorial Day services across Northeast Florida to honor those who made the ultimate sacrifice while serving in the United States armed forces.
Here are some of the different events commemorating Memorial Day this year.
Volunteers step in for families unable to visit fallen heroes Travis Manion Foundation, along with Wounded Warrior Project and AmeriCorps, on Monday hosted the Honor Project, an event where volunteers come together to stand in for military families of the fallen unable to visit their loved ones around Memorial Day.</description></item><item><title>Khloe Kardashian Goes Braless, Bares &amp;quot;Revenge Body&amp;quot; in Women's Health</title><link>/khloe-kardashian-goes-braless-bares-revenge-body-in-womens-health-201548.html</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/khloe-kardashian-goes-braless-bares-revenge-body-in-womens-health-201548.html</guid><description>Who’s in love with the KoKo?! Khloe Kardashian stripped down to nothing but a pair of bikini bottoms and an open shirt on the September 2015 cover of Women’s Health, and revealed in detail about how she achieved that coveted body of hers.
“It started around 2012,” Kardashian said of her incredible physical transformation. “I was having a hard time with Lamar [Odom, her soon-to-be ex-husband]. It was toward the end of our union, and there was so much drama.</description></item><item><title>Kim Kardashian displays her tiny waist and arms in skintight bodysuit after sparking concern with ma</title><link>/kim-kardashian-displays-her-tiny-waist-and-arms-in-skintight-bodysuit-after-sparking-concern-with-major-weight-loss.html</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/kim-kardashian-displays-her-tiny-waist-and-arms-in-skintight-bodysuit-after-sparking-concern-with-major-weight-loss.html</guid><description>KIM Kardashian has flaunted her extremely tiny waist and arms in a skintight bodysuit on Instagram. The reality TV star sparked concern recently from fans with her major weight loss. Kim appeared in Ciara’s Instagram video on July 19, wearing a SKIMS brown bodysuit. Ciara was promoting her new song, Jump featuring Coast Contra, with a star-studded video. It started out with the singer dancing and lip-syncing along to her song, then she put her hand up and the next celebrity appeared on the screen.</description></item><item><title>Jazz player's state Crossword Clue NYT</title><link>/jazz-players-state-crossword-clue-nyt-1027967.html</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/jazz-players-state-crossword-clue-nyt-1027967.html</guid><description>Here is the answer for Jazz player's state NYT Crossword Clue that we have found 1 exact correct answer for Jazz player's state NYT Crossword Clue to help you solve today's Crossword puzzle by V Sruthi | Updated Mar 27, 2023
Source: fresherslive
Jazz player's state&amp;nbsp;CrosswordCheck&amp;nbsp;Jazz player's state&amp;nbsp;Crossword Clue here NYT will publish daily crosswords for the day. Players who are stuck with the Jazz player's state NYT Crossword Clue can head into this page to know the correct answer.</description></item><item><title>In the ___ of (during)</title><link>/in-the-of-during-html.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/in-the-of-during-html.html</guid><description>Crosswords with Friends February 23 2023 In the ___ of (during) General knowledge plays a crucial role in solving crosswords, especially the In the ___ of (during) crossword clue&amp;nbsp;which has appeared on February 23 2023 Crosswords with Friends&amp;nbsp;puzzle. The answer we have shared for In the ___ of (during) has a total of 5 letters but also has other possible answers listed below the main one. Clues often reference historical events, famous personalities, geographical locations, scientific terms, and popular culture.</description></item><item><title>Penny Hardaway and Mary McDonnell</title><link>/penny-hardaway-wife-mary-mcdonnell.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/penny-hardaway-wife-mary-mcdonnell.html</guid><description>Home Penny Hardaway and Mary McDonnell ';return t.replace("ID",e)+a}function lazyLoadYoutubeIframe(){var e=document.createElement("iframe"),t="ID?autoplay=1";t+=0===this.dataset.query.length?'':'&amp;amp;'+this.dataset.query;e.setAttribute("src",t.replace("ID",this.dataset.src)),e.setAttribute("frameborder","0"),e.setAttribute("allowfullscreen","1"),e.setAttribute("allow", "accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture"),this.parentNode.replaceChild(e,this)}document.addEventListener("DOMContentLoaded",function(){var e,t,a=document.getElementsByClassName("rll-youtube-player");for(t=0;tncG1vNJzZmidk5q5pq7RoquypZmnv7C%2BjZympmeVo8GmvtOaoKellaPBcLzEp6WyZZiWv6Wt1pqwZq%2BZm7JuucCrsGalk5m8r7rEpaNomaSprqS0zJ6lrWegmruvxYyhmKuckayuunnAp5tmpZGnxm65wp2mp6aVoblw</description></item><item><title>Chelsea Handler Net Worth: How This Comedic Sensation Built Her Empire!</title><link>/chelsea-handler-net-worth.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/chelsea-handler-net-worth.html</guid><description>Chelsea Handler is a renowned comedian, actress, and television host who has made an indelible mark in the entertainment industry.
With a career spanning decades, her wit and humor have not only won over audiences but also substantially contributed to her net worth.
In this brief exploration, we’ll delve into Chelsea Handler’s impressive financial success and discover just how much she’s amassed over the years.
Chelsea Handler is a famous American comedian, actress, writer, television host, and producer.</description></item><item><title>Like some knowledge and commitments NYT Crossword Clue</title><link>/like-some-knowledge-and-commitments-nyt-crossword-clue-1112002.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/like-some-knowledge-and-commitments-nyt-crossword-clue-1112002.html</guid><description>Here's the answer for Like some knowledge and commitments NYT crossword clue, Answer: PRIOR is the answer for Like some knowledge and commitments crossword clue NYT. by J Nandhini | Updated Jun 23, 2023
Source: fresherslive
Like some knowledge and commitments NYT CrosswordCheck Like some knowledge and commitments Crossword Clue here NYT will publish daily crosswords for the day. Players who are stuck with the Like some knowledge and commitments Crossword Clue can head into this page to know the correct answer.</description></item><item><title>Blue Bloods' Vanessa Ray On The Advice Eddie Would Give Herself</title><link>/blue-bloods-vanessa-ray-on-the-advice-eddie-would-give-herself.html</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blue-bloods-vanessa-ray-on-the-advice-eddie-would-give-herself.html</guid><description>A decade into her job, and Officer Eddie Janko has grown to be a pillar of positive law enforcement. Sure, she is privy to more information than most now that she has a direct line to 1 Police Plaza and its commissioner and her father-in-law. Still, she also has a direct line to the bitterness and jaded mentality of the family. She is constantly trying to introduce positivity into the dinner table conversations.</description></item><item><title>Cardi B Shares a No-Makeup Selfie, Stars Natural Beauty Leaves Netizens Divided</title><link>/149463-cardi-b-shares-a-makeup-selfie-stars-natural-beauty-leaves-netizens-divided.html</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/149463-cardi-b-shares-a-makeup-selfie-stars-natural-beauty-leaves-netizens-divided.html</guid><description>American rapper Cardi B has been trolled for her no-makeup look, which she displayed on her official Twitter pageAfter seeing the photo, people had mixed reactions, with many claiming that the Bodak Yellow hitmaker doesn't look good without makeupOther netizens were still nice enough to leave genuine compliments for the star after other online users tore her apart with huge dragsCardi B has once again demonstrated that she is too real to care about her celebrity image.</description></item><item><title>Trevor Noah Shares His Thoughts on Hosting the Grammys, Mzansi Applauds Comedian: South Africa Is</title><link>/152719-trevor-noah-shares-thoughts-hosting-grammys-mzansi-applauds-comedian-south-africa-proud.html</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/152719-trevor-noah-shares-thoughts-hosting-grammys-mzansi-applauds-comedian-south-africa-proud.html</guid><description>Trevor Noah has taken to social media to share his thoughts on hosting the Grammys for the second time in a rowThe South African comedian rubbed shoulders with some of the best musicians in the world on Sunday nightThe former The Daily Show host thanked everyone for tuning in and also congratulated all the superstars who walked away with a Grammy on the nightTrevor Noah has taken to his timeline to open up about hosting the Grammys for the second time in a row.</description></item><item><title>David Krumholtz Movies and TV Shows: Filmography</title><link>/david-krumholtz-movies-and-tv-shows.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/david-krumholtz-movies-and-tv-shows.html</guid><description>David Krumholtz is an American actor and comedian known for his roles in movies and TV shows. Throughout his career, he has showcased his talent and versatility on the big screen and small screen. Let’s explore his extensive filmography and delve into his diverse acting career.
Key Takeaways: David Krumholtz has appeared in numerous movies and TV shows. His notable film credits include “The Santa Clause” franchise, “10 Things I Hate About You,” and “Hail, Caesar!</description></item><item><title>Hugh Grant, Elizabeth Hurley Reunite 15 Years After Their Split: Pics</title><link>/hugh-grant-elizabeth-hurley-reunite-after-split-pics-2015149.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hugh-grant-elizabeth-hurley-reunite-after-split-pics-2015149.html</guid><description>If only it was Notting Hill! Hugh Grant and his ex Elizabeth Hurley were spotted out together for a casual stroll on Thursday, Sept. 10, in a tree-lined London neighborhood.&amp;nbsp;
The exes, who split in May 2000, appeared friendly as Grant, 55, wore white gym shorts with a navy jacket and Hurley, 50, sported a gray sweater with jeans and boots.&amp;nbsp;
As photographers snapped away, The Man From U.N.C.L.E. star appeared to be back to his lady-loving antics as he turned to stare at a girl in short shorts while talking to the Royals actress and model.</description></item><item><title>Buzz Aldrin Net Worth: How Much Is the Second Man on the Moon Worth?</title><link>/buzz-aldrin-net-worth-how-much-is-the-second-man-on-the-moon-worth.html</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/buzz-aldrin-net-worth-how-much-is-the-second-man-on-the-moon-worth.html</guid><description>Aldrin is a legendary American astronaut who was the second person to walk on the moon after Neil Armstrong in 1969.
He is also an engineer, a fighter pilot, a best-selling author, and a space advocate.
But how much is Buzz Aldrin’s net worth in 2023?
According to source Net Worth, Buzz Aldrin’s net worth is estimated to be around $12 million as of September 2023.
This is based on his income from his military and NASA careers, his book royalties, his public appearances, and his investments.</description></item><item><title>Boston's Top 50 Athletes of All-Time | News, Scores, Highlights, Stats, and Rumors</title><link>/438166-bostons-top-50-athletes-of-all-time.html</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/438166-bostons-top-50-athletes-of-all-time.html</guid><description>Considered by many the greatest hitter of all-time, Ted Williams presents an interesting case to be considered the greatest athlete in Boston history. Williams is the last MLB player to hit .400 in a single season (.406) and holds the highest career batting average of any player with 500 or more home runs (.344).
Williams served in the military during World War II and those four years of absence from the game are likely the greatest aberration in the history of sports.</description></item><item><title>Download Video Star for iOS - Free</title><link>/video-star.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/video-star.html</guid><description>Star in your own music videoIt’s showtime. Produce your music videos, edit, and add effects from one place.Video Star, is a music video maker. You air guitar in the shower and you dance along to the radio during your commute. When music is that much a part of your life, don’t you need an app to reflect all your musical know-how? Be the star of your own video.
With Video Star, you don’t need to have an amazing singing voice.</description></item><item><title>49ers' Nick Bosa Wins 2022-23 NFL Defensive Player of the Year Award | News, Scores, Highlights, Sta</title><link>/10062328-49ers-nick-bosa-wins-2022-23-nfl-defensive-player-of-the-year-award.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/10062328-49ers-nick-bosa-wins-2022-23-nfl-defensive-player-of-the-year-award.html</guid><description>Ezra Shaw/Getty ImagesSan Francisco 49ers edge-rusher Nick Bosa has won the Associated Press Defensive Player of the Year award for the first time in his career.
San Francisco 49ers @49ersNever a doubt ¯\_(ツ)_/¯&amp;lt;a href="https://twitter.com/nbsmallerbear?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw"&amp;gt;@nbsmallerbear&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; is the AP Defensive Player of the Year. &amp;lt;a href="https://t.co/SddNXf70GA"&amp;gt;pic.twitter.com/SddNXf70GA&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;
NFL @NFLA well-deserved honor for the DPOY &amp;lt;a href="https://twitter.com/nbsmallerbear?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw"&amp;gt;@nbsmallerbear&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; 👏&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;📺: &amp;lt;a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/NFLHonors?src=hash&amp;amp;amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw"&amp;gt;#NFLHonors&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; on NBC &amp;lt;a href="https://t.co/kJXZie0LOC"&amp;gt;pic.twitter.com/kJXZie0LOC&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;
Bosa nearly won the award unanimously:
Ari Meirov @MySportsUpdateDefensive Player of the Year voting:&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;- Nick Bosa: 46&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;- Haason Reddick: 2&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;- Quinnen Williams: 1&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;- Chris Jones: 1&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;Micah Parsons did not get a single first-place vote.</description></item><item><title>Astrology Birth Chart of Talinda Ann Bentley (Family Member) 2024</title><link>/talinda-ann-bentley-19760918-html.html</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/talinda-ann-bentley-19760918-html.html</guid><description>Astrology Birth chart of Talinda Ann Bentley (also known as a natal chart) is like a map that provides a snapshot of all the planetary coordinates at the exact time of Talinda Ann Bentley's birth. Every individual’s birth chart is completely unique. The birthplace, date, and time of Talinda Ann Bentley's birth are what is needed to calculate Talinda Ann Bentley's birth chart.
The aspects describe the geometric angles between the planets.</description></item><item><title>Kourtney Kardashian and Scott Disick Preparing to Get Married</title><link>/kourtney-kardashian-scott-disick-preparing-get-married.html</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/kourtney-kardashian-scott-disick-preparing-get-married.html</guid><description>The Lord and his Lady are finally tying the knot?
If you follow the Kardashians you probably never thought you’d see the day that Kourtney Kardashian and Scott Disick would actually get married. The parents of two adorable children has always held the position that they weren’t or had no interested in the ritual of marriage. Looks like that has all changed…
According to RadarOnline, Kardashian and Disick are planning a wedding in Punta Cana, Mexico at the estate of Girls Gone Wild peddler Joe Francis.</description></item><item><title>Golden Bachelor Renee Job Family And Wikipedia</title><link>/golden-bachelor-renee-job-family-and-wikipedia.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/golden-bachelor-renee-job-family-and-wikipedia.html</guid><description>Golden&amp;nbsp;Bachelor Renee has gained a following worldwide because of her endearing personality.
Despite her continued discretion over her family, we know she is a loving grandma and a dedicated mother of two, with her kids serving as her steadfast support.
Viewers anxiously expect the scene after an interview about a sweet meeting between her grandkids and Gerry Turner, The Golden Bachelor. Renee’s previous relationship is still a mystery despite her references to a kind ex-husband.</description></item><item><title>Below Deck's Hannah Ferrier: Where is she now?</title><link>/below-decks-hannah-ferrier-where-is-she-now.html</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/below-decks-hannah-ferrier-where-is-she-now.html</guid><description>HANNAH Ferrier rose to fame in 2016 after joining the cast of Bravo’s Below Deck Mediterranean.
For five seasons, she worked under Captain Sandy Yawn but was fired from the franchise in 2020.
Where is Hannah Ferrier now?Hannah Ferrier is known for her career as a Chief Stewardess and rose to fame after starring in Below Deck Mediterranean.
Despite being a fan favorite, the Sydney, Australia, native was fired in 2020 after she was caught with Valium on board during season 5, according to Us Weekly.</description></item><item><title>You Season 5: Netflix Release Date, Cast, Plot, Trailer, And More Information For You To Know!</title><link>/you-season-3-netflix-release-date-cast-plot-update-trailer.html</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/you-season-3-netflix-release-date-cast-plot-update-trailer.html</guid><description>“Reading Caroline’s novel, Greg and I were instantly obsessed with Joe Goldberg and his twisted world view. And it’s been thrilling to watch Penn bring Joe to creepy yet compelling life. We’re deeply grateful that Netflix has shown You such monumental support and that people around the world have enjoyed watching Joe really get it all very wrong over the past 3 seasons. The whole You team is excited to explore new, dark facets of love in season 4.</description></item><item><title>Andy Grammer Net Worth, Age, Height, Bio, Birthday, Wiki!</title><link>/andy-grammer.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/andy-grammer.html</guid><description>Explore Andy Grammer net worth, age, height, bio, birthday, wiki, and salary! In this article, we will discover how old is Andy Grammer? Who is Andy Grammer dating now &amp;amp; how much money does Andy Grammer have?
Andy Grammer BiographyAndy Grammer is one of the most popular and richest R&amp;amp;B Singer who was born on December 3, 1983 in Los Angeles, California, United States. American R&amp;amp;B singer whose self-titled 2011 album charted at #1 on the U.</description></item><item><title>Lisa of The Cosby Show and A Different World</title><link>/lisa-of-the-cosby-show-and-a-different-world-html.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/lisa-of-the-cosby-show-and-a-different-world-html.html</guid><description>Crosswords with Friends August 18 2020 Lisa of The Cosby Show and A Different World General knowledge plays a crucial role in solving crosswords, especially the Lisa of The Cosby Show and A Different World crossword clue&amp;nbsp;which has appeared on August 18 2020 Crosswords with Friends&amp;nbsp;puzzle. The answer we have shared for Lisa of The Cosby Show and A Different World has a total of 5 letters but also has other possible answers listed below the main one.</description></item><item><title>Pete Wentz, Meagan Camper Welcome Baby Boy</title><link>/pete-wentz-meagan-camper-welcome-baby-boy-2014218.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/pete-wentz-meagan-camper-welcome-baby-boy-2014218.html</guid><description>Pete Wentz is a dad again! The Fall Out Boy rocker and his girlfriend Meagan Camper welcomed their first child together, a baby boy, on Wednesday, Aug. 20, his rep confirms to Us Weekly.
"Mom and baby are happy and healthy. They are thrilled at the addition to the family and Bronx is over the moon to be a big brother," his rep tells Us of the new edition to their family, who they named Saint Lazslo.</description></item><item><title>Pretty Little Liars' Vanessa Ray: I Didn't Find Out I Was A Until June</title><link>/pretty-little-liars-vanessa-ray-i-didnt-find-out-i-was-a-until-june-2015128.html</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/pretty-little-liars-vanessa-ray-i-didnt-find-out-i-was-a-until-june-2015128.html</guid><description>Pretty Little Liars‘ big “A” reveal was just as shocking to the actress playing the show’s ultimate villain as it was to the audiences who watched it play out on Tuesday, Aug. 11. Vanessa Ray tells Us Weekly the morning after the answer-filled episode aired that she didn’t even know her character, CeCe, was A until just before shooting the Season 6A finale.
“I didn’t find out until right before we started filming,” she admits to Us.</description></item><item><title>Harry Wayne Casey Enjoys Entertaining Family and Friends in His Spanish-Style Home</title><link>/harry-wayne-casey-enjoys-entertaining-family-and-friends-in-his-spanish-style-home-52760.html</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/harry-wayne-casey-enjoys-entertaining-family-and-friends-in-his-spanish-style-home-52760.html</guid><description>He’s traveled the world with KC and the Sunshine Band, but for singer-songwriter Harry Wayne Casey, there’s no place he’d rather get down tonight than in his beloved Miami.
“I grew up about 10 minutes from here,” Harry shares with ‘Closer.’ “This area used to be a dairy farm and we’d play here as kids. All my family is in the area and I wanted to be near them.”
Harry performing in July 1977.</description></item><item><title>Orange Cake {Moist &amp;amp; Flavorful}</title><link>/orange-cake.html</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/orange-cake.html</guid><description>Home » Cake &amp;amp; Cupcakes » Orange Cake Published: Jan 7, 2022 by Allison · 36 Comments
Pin Share Email This homemade Orange Cake is bursting with the flavor of fresh oranges. A combination of orange zest and orange juice make this cake extra moist and flavorful. This bundt cake can be enjoyed for breakfast, dessert, or alongside a cup of afternoon tea.</description></item><item><title>SINGLE REVIEW: Selena Gomez 'Same Old Love'</title><link>/single-review-selena-gomez-same-old-love.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/single-review-selena-gomez-same-old-love.html</guid><description>Selena Gomez is teasing fans about the release of her new album ‘Revival’ by releasing the teaser track ‘Same Old Love’.
The follow up to the smash hit ‘Good For You’ is the perfect break-up song.
While ‘Good For You’ was all about that new love feeling ‘Same Old Love’ sees Selena taking a swipe at an ex and expressing she is sick of that ‘Same Old Love’.
The new track proves how diverse the ‘Revival’ LP will be and showcases Gomez’s sweet vocals.</description></item><item><title>Manatee County School District Calendar</title><link>/manatee-county-school-district-calendar.html</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/manatee-county-school-district-calendar.html</guid><description>This article will help the students get Manatee County School District Calendar and also guides parents on important dates to note
About The Manatee County School District is a public school district located in Manatee County, Florida, United States. It serves the educational needs of approximately 48,000 students across 62 schools.
The district’s mission is to educate and develop all students academically, socially, and emotionally so that they may acquire the skills and knowledge necessary to succeed in a changing world.</description></item><item><title>Tyron Lambert allegedly murdered wife Jasmyn Lambert</title><link>/tyron-lambert-allegedly-murdered-wife-jasmyn-lambert.html</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/tyron-lambert-allegedly-murdered-wife-jasmyn-lambert.html</guid><description>Tyron Lambert, on the left, and Jasmyn Lambert, on the right. (Paulding County Sheriff’s Office; Still Elementary/Cobb County Schools)
A beloved Georgia elementary school teacher is dead and her estranged husband faces myriad criminal charges after two calls to the sheriff’s office within a matter of hours couldn’t stop the alleged violence.
Tyron Victor Lambert, 42, stands accused of one count each of murder – family violence, malice murder, home invasion – burglary, criminal damage to property, obstruction, and criminal trespass as well as two counts each of cruelty to children, aggravated assault, and possession of a firearm in the commission of a crime, according to a press release issued by the Paulding County Sheriff’s Office.</description></item><item><title>Emotionally Immature Parents</title><link>/emotionally-immature-parents.html</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/emotionally-immature-parents.html</guid><description>Dealing with parents who aren’t good at handling feelings can be tough. It affects you when you’re a kid and even when you grow up. These emotionally immature parents might act like they’re younger than they are, making things more complicated.
Types of Emotionally Immature Parents Self-Centered Parents: They care more about themselves and don’t payattention to what you need or how you feel. Passive-Aggressive Parent: They show their anger in sneaky ways, like making you feel guilty.</description></item><item><title>1600 Pennsylvania ___ (the White House's street address): Abbr.</title><link>/1600-pennsylvania-the-white-houses-street-address-abbr-html.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/1600-pennsylvania-the-white-houses-street-address-abbr-html.html</guid><description>Crosswords with Friends July 31 2023 1600 Pennsylvania ___ (the White House's street address): Abbr. General knowledge plays a crucial role in solving crosswords, especially the 1600 Pennsylvania ___ (the White House's street address): Abbr. crossword clue&amp;nbsp;which has appeared on July 31 2023 Crosswords with Friends&amp;nbsp;puzzle. The answer we have shared for 1600 Pennsylvania ___ (the White House's street address): Abbr. has a total of 3 letters but also has other possible answers listed below the main one.</description></item><item><title>Mdchen Amick Married Life with David Alexis As Impressive With The Years,Facing Nude Scene? Know a</title><link>/madchen-amick-married-life-david-alexis-know-husband-children-wiki.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/madchen-amick-married-life-david-alexis-know-husband-children-wiki.html</guid><description>Everybody wishes for a perfect partner to get married and live a long happy conjugal life. But only a few&amp;nbsp;are lucky enough to have such experience. Further, having a person that shares a similar&amp;nbsp;passion is hard to find. Well, Twin Peaks actress Madchen Amick,46, and her husband David Alexis are few of those people. Moreover, they have been happily married for more than 24 years with two impressive children to the family.</description></item><item><title>Fantasy Football 2023: 5-Round Standard League Mock Draft | News, Scores, Highlights, Stats, and Rum</title><link>/10087921-fantasy-football-2023-5-round-standard-league-mock-draft.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/10087921-fantasy-football-2023-5-round-standard-league-mock-draft.html</guid><description>Mitchell Leff/Getty Images31. Miles Sanders, RB, Carolina Panthers
32. Jalen Hurts, QB, Philadelphia Eagles
33. Calvin Ridley, WR, Jacksonville Jaguars
34. Lamar Jackson, QB, Baltimore Ravens
35. Rhamondre Stevenson, RB, New England Patriots
36. Jonathan Taylor, RB, Indianapolis Colts
37. Dameon Pierce, RB, Houston Texans
38. Cam Akers, RB, Los Angeles Rams
39. Mark Andrews, TE, Baltimore Ravens
40. Kenneth Walker III, RB, Seattle Seahawks
Best value: Jalen Hurts, QB, Philadelphia Eagles</description></item><item><title>Cunk on Earth Is Set To Released On Netflix</title><link>/cunk-on-earth-is-set-to-released-on-netflix.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/cunk-on-earth-is-set-to-released-on-netflix.html</guid><description>According to CinemaBlend, a new mockumentary series named Cunk on Earth will premiere on Netflix on Tuesday, January 31, 2023, at 3.01 a.m. ET. The plot revolves around an investigative journalist who embarks on an epic adventure across human history. Diane Morgan stars as Philomena Cunk in Cunk on Earth, with numerous others playing crucial supporting parts. Charlie Brooker, the creator of Black Mirror, is in charge of the program.</description></item><item><title>Happy National Brothers Day! Here Are 6 Sets of Stars You Didnt Know Had Brothers With Claims</title><link>/happy-national-brothers-day-here-are-6-sets-of-stars-you-didnt-know-had-brothers-with-claims-to-fame.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/happy-national-brothers-day-here-are-6-sets-of-stars-you-didnt-know-had-brothers-with-claims-to-fame.html</guid><description>May 24 marks National Brother’s Day and this year, Atlanta Black Star is commemorating the event by recognizing the brothers — big and little — of the stars who unexpectedly have male siblings in show biz. Founded by C. Daniel Rhodes, the annual event is a time where the famous and non-famous alike can acknowledge the bond they have with their brothers.
Syleena Johnson and Chad “Ochocinco” Johnson Syleena Johnson may be the singer of the family but when it comes to football, her brother Chad Johnson takes the cake.</description></item><item><title>Sam Hurley Age | Wiki, Net worth, Bio, Height, Girlfriend (UPDATED)</title><link>/sam-hurley.html</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/sam-hurley.html</guid><description>Date of BirthSeptember 1, 2003Age20 years oldBirthplaceUnited StatesZodiacVirgoNationalityAmericanEthnicityMulti-racialProfessionTikTok star, Social Media StarHeight5 feet 8 inches (1.73 m)Relationship statusSingleNet worth$600,000 – $700,000 (More info Below)Sam Hurley has swept the TikTok globe, and TikTok has swept the world of TikTok. Sam is one of the rising stars with a viral following, and his popularity has reached 3.7 million. Sam has been posting videos demonstrating his originality, comedy, and personality, so don’t mistake him for just another TikTok celebrity.</description></item><item><title>When Mother's Day is</title><link>/when-mothers-day-is-html.html</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/when-mothers-day-is-html.html</guid><description>Crosswords with Friends November 12 2020 When Mother's Day is General knowledge plays a crucial role in solving crosswords, especially the When Mother's Day is crossword clue&amp;nbsp;which has appeared on November 12 2020 Crosswords with Friends&amp;nbsp;puzzle. The answer we have shared for When Mother's Day is has a total of 3 letters but also has other possible answers listed below the main one. Clues often reference historical events, famous personalities, geographical locations, scientific terms, and popular culture.</description></item><item><title>LOL!Jessica Alba Meets a Fan With Her Face Tattooed on His Arm</title><link>/jessica-alba-kate-hudson-kids-taylor-swift-concert-photos-68030.html</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/jessica-alba-kate-hudson-kids-taylor-swift-concert-photos-68030.html</guid><description>Talk about a meta moment! Jessica Alba recently ran into a fan on the street — and the police officer showed the 35-year-old star that he has her face tattooed on his arm. The best part? The actress documented the funny meet-and-greet on Instagram! MORE: Drew Barrymore Gets a New Tattoo of Her Daughters’ Names — See the Pic!
“Definitely one of the more surreal moments of my life. This sweetie pie young officer drove by outside my friend’s house and stopped to tell me he had my face tattooed on his arm — of course I HAD to see it!</description></item><item><title>See Cher Walk the Runway in Surprise Fashion Week Appearance</title><link>/cher-balmain-fashion-week-news.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/cher-balmain-fashion-week-news.html</guid><description>The "stage was calling," so she had no choice but to answer. At least, that's how Cher explained her surprise runway appearance at Balmain's spring 2023 show on Sept. 28. The 76-year-old singer and actor closed out the show, which was part of Paris Fashion Week, appearing alongside designer Olivier Rousteing and rocking a skin-tight metallic bodysuit. The legend&amp;nbsp;went on to post her feelings about the experience on Twitter. Read on to see Cher's runway look and to find out more about her surprise modeling moment.</description></item><item><title>Alice Braga Married, Husband, Net Worth, Nationality, Measurements, Wiki</title><link>/alice-braga-married-husband-net-worth-wiki-bio.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/alice-braga-married-husband-net-worth-wiki-bio.html</guid><description>Have you watched the TV series Queen of South? Do you know the main character, Teresa Mendoza? She is not only beautiful but thrives in a male-dominated drug world. Well, the queen is non-other than the Brazilian born star Alice Braga. Her face is familiar on the TV thanks to her success in other American and Brazilian films as well. Let’s get down to some facts about her husband, net worth, measurements, and her nationality.</description></item><item><title>That's dazzling!</title><link>/thats-dazzling-html.html</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/thats-dazzling-html.html</guid><description>Crosswords with Friends May 24 2022 That's dazzling! General knowledge plays a crucial role in solving crosswords, especially the That's dazzling! crossword clue&amp;nbsp;which has appeared on May 24 2022 Crosswords with Friends&amp;nbsp;puzzle. The answer we have shared for That's dazzling! has a total of 3 letters but also has other possible answers listed below the main one. Clues often reference historical events, famous personalities, geographical locations, scientific terms, and popular culture.</description></item><item><title>Flume and Tove Lo Debut Music Video For 'Say It'</title><link>/flume-tove-lo-debut-music-video-say.html</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/flume-tove-lo-debut-music-video-say.html</guid><description>The music video for Flume’s “Say It&amp;nbsp;” featuring Tove Lo has finally arrived, and It is gravity-defying!
The video, directed by Nez features a woman gracefully floating on the side of a building, as well as an astronaut like figure, that performs a series of gravity-defying acrobatics against the surface of a skyscraper.
“Don’t doubt me babe
You make me wanna change
Break my bed to make me wanna stay” – sings Tove Lo And even though the Aussie producer and Swedish singer are nowhere to be seen, it doesn’t make the video&amp;nbsp;any&amp;nbsp;less stunning and ethereal.</description></item><item><title>Ashley Graham celebrates having 'mommy friends' including Iskra Lawrence and Emily Ratajkowski</title><link>/ashley-graham-celebrates-having-mommy-friends-including-iskra-lawrence-and-emily-ratajkowski.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/ashley-graham-celebrates-having-mommy-friends-including-iskra-lawrence-and-emily-ratajkowski.html</guid><description>Ashley Graham loves having so many new ‘mommy friends’.
The 33-year-old model welcomed her son Isaac into the world in January 2020, and since then several of her supermodel friends – including Iskra Lawrence, Gigi Hadid, Emily Ratajkowski, and Karlie Kloss – have also welcomed children.
Speaking about her pals-turned-moms, Ashley said: ‘It’s amazing how many mommy friends I have now. They just appeared.
Ashley Graham loves having so many new ‘mommy friends’: She welcomed her son Isaac in 2020, and since then several of her supermodel friends – including Iskra Lawrence, pictured with her here in 2016 – have also welcomed children</description></item><item><title>Former Ulster Unionist Party leader David Trimble has died aged 77 following a 'short illness'</title><link>/former-ulster-unionist-party-leader-david-trimble-has-died-aged-77-following-a-short-illness.html</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/former-ulster-unionist-party-leader-david-trimble-has-died-aged-77-following-a-short-illness.html</guid><description>Former Ulster Unionist Party leader David Trimble has died at age 77, the party has revealed.&amp;nbsp;
In a statement on behalf of the Trimble family, the UUP said: ‘It is with great sadness that the family of Lord Trimble announce that he passed away peacefully earlier today following a short illness.’
Trimble and John Hume, former leader of the Catholic Social Democratic and Labour Party, jointly received the Nobel Peace Prize in 1998 for their roles in helping end more than 30 years of bloodshed.</description></item><item><title>11 Real-Life Murders That Were Inspired By Horror Movies</title><link>/murders-inspired-by-horror-movies.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/murders-inspired-by-horror-movies.html</guid><description>Jeffrey Dahmer And The Exorcist III Morgan Creek EntertainmentDahmer would fall into a trance and moan while watching The Exorcist III (1990).
Infamous for committing the worst serial killings in Wisconsin’s history, Jeffrey Dahmer murdered 17 boys and young men between 1974 and 1978. When authorities finally raided his Milwaukee apartment on July 22, 1991, and arrested him, they found four heads, three skulls, and the remains of 11 people in his fridge.</description></item><item><title>Alternative Sports Websites Changing The Way Readers Get Their Sport Fix | News, Scores, Highlights,</title><link>/65198-alternative-sports-websiteschanging-the-way-readers-get-their-sport-fix.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/65198-alternative-sports-websiteschanging-the-way-readers-get-their-sport-fix.html</guid><description>ESPN.com and Yahoo! Sports routinely attract tens of millions of unique visitors each month, but alternative websites that most sports fans have never heard of are quickly catching up.
Those alternative websites generally get grouped together in a diverse group of websites known as sports blogs. They range in terms of variety from sports news aggregators like Deadspin, a site that receives upwards of ten million unique hits each month, to humor sites with obscenity warnings like Kissing Suzy Kolber, a blog that makes fun of all things NFL.</description></item><item><title>Hannaha Hall from The Chi Age and Biography</title><link>/hannaha-hall.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hannaha-hall.html</guid><description>Hannaha Hall is a famous artist and online media face. Her confident and energetic style made Ms. Hall the face of many brands and movies. She conveys a positive message to her fans and followers through social media, giving them the ability to think about themselves. Let’s find more about such an amazing personality.
Hannaha Hall Age and Early lifeHannaha grew up in Chicago. Now, she is 22 years old. She is an American with a mixed accent.</description></item><item><title>Thomas Gold Makes Your &amp;quot;Wildest Dream&amp;quot; Come True On New Single</title><link>/thomas-gold-wildest-dream.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/thomas-gold-wildest-dream.html</guid><description>German DJ and producer Thomas Gold is back with a brand new release and it is the perfect track to kick-start our weekend.
After headlining shows at Ultra, EDC and Coachella as well as remixing the latest tracks by Hardwell, Connor Maynard and more, the DJ is now back with a brand new original release.
Titled “Wildest Dream”, Gold’s latest song sees him teaming up with Kosling and singer-songwriter Matthew Steeper.</description></item><item><title>Fovos Take On Masked Wolfs Butterflies &amp;amp; Bandaids In A Drum N Bass Fuelled Remix</title><link>/new-zealand-duo-fovos-take-on-masked-wolfs-butterflies-bandaids-in-a-drum-n-bass-fuelled-remix.html</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/new-zealand-duo-fovos-take-on-masked-wolfs-butterflies-bandaids-in-a-drum-n-bass-fuelled-remix.html</guid><description>FOVOS step up as Masked Wolf calls on the emerging New Zealand duo for an official remix of his 2022 hit ‘Butterflies &amp;amp; Bandaids’ on Teamwrk Records.&amp;nbsp;Australian musician Masked Wolf became a global name after the viral success of his 2021 smash hit&amp;nbsp;‘Astronaut in the Ocean’&amp;nbsp;which accumulated&amp;nbsp;over 1 billion streams&amp;nbsp;on Spotify alone.
Debuting as a moody hip-hop track, ‘Butterflies &amp;amp; Bandaids’ boasts Masked Wolf’s quintessential raspy vocals on hard-hitting introspective lyrics.</description></item><item><title>Scarlxrd</title><link>/scarlxrd.html</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/scarlxrd.html</guid><description>Learn about Scarlxrd Net Worth, Biography, Age, Birthday, Height, Early Life, Family, Dating, Partner, Wiki and Facts.
Who is Scarlxrd:Scarlxrd is a famous Rapper. He was born on June 19, 1994 and his birthplace is Wolverhampton, England. Scarlxrd is also well known as, YouTube phenomenon turned rapper who became known for his hit channel TheMazziMaz where he uploads comedic videos about a variety of topics. He worked with Myth City to release an EP under the band’s name in February 2015.</description></item><item><title>WWE's Paul Heyman: John Cena Had to Be Talked into Making Make-A-Wish Visits Public | News, Scores,</title><link>/10078670-wwes-paul-heyman-john-cena-had-to-be-talked-into-making-make-a-wish-visits-public.html</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/10078670-wwes-paul-heyman-john-cena-had-to-be-talked-into-making-make-a-wish-visits-public.html</guid><description>Michael Loccisano/Getty ImagesJohn Cena's countless hours of work meeting with Make-A-Wish children is no secret.
It turns out that wasn't Cena's call.
According to Paul Heyman, Cena never wanted to make those visits public.
"I don't have the words to convey the admiration I have for John Cena as a human being," Heyman said on Rick Rubin's Tetragrammaton podcast (h/t Wrestling News' Michael Schrute).
"There had to come a point in time where Vince had to sit down with John and say, 'You need to let me go public with these Make-A-Wish visits.</description></item><item><title>'Ragnarok' Star Resa Saffa Park Releases Mesmerizing Tendencies</title><link>/ragnarok-star-resa-saffa-park-releases-mesmerizing-tendencies.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/ragnarok-star-resa-saffa-park-releases-mesmerizing-tendencies.html</guid><description>Norwegian singer-songwriter and actress Resa Saffa Park drops her brand-new music video, “Tendencies,” a track from her EP, Spaces, via Unity Records &amp;amp; Propellor Recordings.
Talking about Spaces, Resa shares, “The EP is a collection of thoughts and feelings I’ve had related to distance, space, gaps, and loss. How we as individuals associate and link to one another and how we navigate in different rooms, boxes: spaces.”
Resa, aka Theresa Frostad Eggesbø, starred as Sonja in SKAM, followed by her role as Saxa in Netflix’s series Ragnarok.</description></item><item><title>Colleen Ballinger Controversy Drama Gets Shocking Reaction on Twitter after Colleen Vlogs Apology</title><link>/colleen-ballinger-controversy-drama-gets-shocking-reaction-on-twitter.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/colleen-ballinger-controversy-drama-gets-shocking-reaction-on-twitter.html</guid><description>Best known for her online persona, Miranda Sings, Colleen’s comedic genius, and distinctive vocal stylings have garnered a massive following. Her hilarious videos, where she humorously portrays a self-absorbed and off-key aspiring singer, have gained worldwide recognition, showcasing her exceptional comedic timing and improvisational skills.&amp;nbsp;
At present, Colleen is in trouble because a person named Adama has made very serious allegations against her. Fans want to know what happened to Colleen.</description></item><item><title>Chris Brown: Only Singer to Be in Prison With No. 1 Record at Same Tim</title><link>/chris-brown-25-things-2015278.html</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/chris-brown-25-things-2015278.html</guid><description>The Grammy Award winning singer Chris Brown, who’s currently on his One Hell of a Nite Tour through Sept. 19, shared 25 surprising and some admirable facts about himself with Us Weekly.
1. I am a neat freak.
2. I listen to Sango and Hippie Sabotage on Pandora.
3. I’m the only singer who has been incarcerated and had a No. 1 record at the same time.
4. I’ve trained in martial arts and boxing.</description></item><item><title>Teen Missing Since September Is Thought To Be Sex Trafficking Victim</title><link>/corinna-slusser-missing-teen-pimp-assault.html</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/corinna-slusser-missing-teen-pimp-assault.html</guid><description>“She's so sweet and so naive. She didn't know what she was getting herself into.” Corinna Slusser, 19.
New reports revealed that a girl that went missing in Queens, N.Y. nearly two months ago filed an assault complaint with the NYPD shortly before she disappeared. The New York Daily News reported that 19-year-old Corinna Slusser filed an assault complaint against a man believed to be her pimp on Aug. 28, just two weeks before she was reported missing.</description></item><item><title>Tori Spelling Suffers Burns After Falling Onto Grill at Benihana</title><link>/tori-spelling-suffers-burns-after-falling-onto-grill-at-benihana-2015144.html</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/tori-spelling-suffers-burns-after-falling-onto-grill-at-benihana-2015144.html</guid><description>Not the kind of experience she was looking for! On Sunday, April 5, Tori Spelling and her family celebrated Easter with a trip to their local Benihana restaurant, indulging in the chain’s signature teppanyaki delicacies.&amp;nbsp;
Unfortunately for the reality star, 41, her festive meal took a painful turn when she tripped and fell onto the hibachi grill, according to multiple outlets, as first reported by The Daily Mail. Spelling’s husband Dean McDermott confirmed to the New York Daily News that his wife burned her arm on the steaming grill and required medical care to treat the burns.</description></item><item><title>Eugene Sheffer Author Bagnold 4 letters Crossword Clue Answers</title><link>/eugene-sheffer-author-bagnold-4-letters-crossword-clue-answers-1226308.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/eugene-sheffer-author-bagnold-4-letters-crossword-clue-answers-1226308.html</guid><description>Here is the Possible Answers for Author Bagnold Eugene Sheffer Crossword Clue that We have found 1 correct answer for Author Bagnold Crossword Clue Eugene Sheffer with 4 letters letters to help you solve today's Eugene Sheffer Crossword puzzle. Author Bagnold Crossword Clue Eugene Sheffer AnswerFinding difficult to guess the answer for Author Bagnold Crossword Clue, then we will help you with the correct answer. Crosswords are sometimes simple sometimes difficult to guess.</description></item><item><title>Sponsored Tweet from LeBron James Reportedly Worth $140,000 | News, Scores, Highlights, Stats, and R</title><link>/2551786-sponsored-tweet-from-lebron-james-reportedly-worth-140000.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/2551786-sponsored-tweet-from-lebron-james-reportedly-worth-140000.html</guid><description>Evan Vucci/Associated PressA sponsored tweet from LeBron James,&amp;nbsp;with a reach of 23.2 million followers, seems like a surefire way to get your product or service on the map—but you better be prepared to cough up $140,000.
The exact value of $139,474&amp;nbsp;was determined by Opendorse, a company that helps marketers configure digital and social media endorsement campaigns with athletes. It's the highest value of any U.S. athlete as estimated by the company, leading second- and third-ranked Kevin Durant&amp;nbsp;($66,553) and Kobe Bryant&amp;nbsp;($42,389) by a long shot.</description></item><item><title>Donovan McNabb Benched: 10 Reasons Why McNabb and the Redskins Are Done | News, Scores, Highlights,</title><link>/546536-donovan-mcnabb-benched-10-reasons-why-mcnabb-and-the-redskins-are-done.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/546536-donovan-mcnabb-benched-10-reasons-why-mcnabb-and-the-redskins-are-done.html</guid><description>Mitchell Layton/Getty ImagesI think that from the beginning Shanahan didn't like McNabb in Washington.&amp;nbsp;
I think that Shanahan did not belive that McNabb could get the job done.&amp;nbsp;
I think that Shanahan is looking for other QB's at any cost.&amp;nbsp;
I think that Shanahan will throw McNabb under the bus to save himself.&amp;nbsp;
It has reached the point over the course of the season in Washington, that this relationship is beyond repair.</description></item><item><title>Get Noticed and Gain Followers with These Short and Eye-Catching IG Aesthetic Bios! Boost Your Insta</title><link>/get-noticed-and-gain-followers-with-these-short-and-eye-catching-ig-aesthetic-bios-boost-your-instagram-profile-today.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/get-noticed-and-gain-followers-with-these-short-and-eye-catching-ig-aesthetic-bios-boost-your-instagram-profile-today.html</guid><description>Looking to enhance your Instagram aesthetic? Look no further than our Bio IG Aesthetic Singkat &amp;amp; Dijamin Menarik Banyak Followers! Our viral video full of tips and tricks is guaranteed to captivate your audience and attract a multitude of followers. Don’t miss out on this opportunity to take your Instagram game to the next level!
Maybe you are interested Shahid Latif Shot To Death Video Gone Viral And Family el Guason de Tamaulipas Video sin censura Samantha Rodriguez Accident: How Did It Happen?</description></item><item><title>I need a warmer coat!</title><link>/i-need-a-warmer-coat-html.html</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/i-need-a-warmer-coat-html.html</guid><description>Crosswords with Friends February 12 2022 I need a warmer coat! General knowledge plays a crucial role in solving crosswords, especially the I need a warmer coat! crossword clue&amp;nbsp;which has appeared on February 12 2022 Crosswords with Friends&amp;nbsp;puzzle. The answer we have shared for I need a warmer coat! has a total of 3 letters but also has other possible answers listed below the main one. Clues often reference historical events, famous personalities, geographical locations, scientific terms, and popular culture.</description></item><item><title>Lily James ditches her blonde wig after filming Pam and Tommy with co-star Sebastian Stan</title><link>/lily-james-ditches-her-blonde-wig-after-filming-pam-and-tommy-with-co-star-sebastian-stan.html</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/lily-james-ditches-her-blonde-wig-after-filming-pam-and-tommy-with-co-star-sebastian-stan.html</guid><description>They’re set to portray Pamela Anderson and Tommy Lee in a new Hulu series.
And Lily James and her co-star Sebastian Stan, 38, were seen heading to their trailers after a busy day of filming in Los Angeles, California, on Friday.
The actress, 32, was seen ditching her blonde wig in favour of her natural brunette locks as she went out for a stroll during a break from set.&amp;nbsp;
Quick change: Lily James ditched her blonde wig for her natural brunette locks as she headed to her trailer during a break from filming Pam and Tommy with Sebastian Stan in LA on Friday</description></item><item><title>Beyonces 10 Most Viewed Music Videos of All Time, Ranked</title><link>/beyonces-10-most-viewed-music-videos-of-all-time-ranked.html</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/beyonces-10-most-viewed-music-videos-of-all-time-ranked.html</guid><description>Beyoncé is coming.
The superstar stopped the world with the announcement of her forthcoming album Renaissance on Thursday (June 16), and now, fans are excitedly discussing what’s to come – as well as looking back at all the incredible songs and music videos she’s already provided the BeyHive.
We’ve rounded up the 10 most popular music videos on Bey‘s YouTube, including the No. 1 most popular song, which has over a billion views.</description></item><item><title>From ___ to bottom</title><link>/from-to-bottom-html.html</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/from-to-bottom-html.html</guid><description>• A child's toy, commonly in the form of a conoid or pear, made to spin on its point, usually by drawing off a string wound round its surface or stem, the motion being sometimes continued by means of a whip. • A plug, or conical block of wood, with longitudital grooves on its surface, in which the strands of the rope slide in the process of twisting. • The highest part of anything; the upper end, edge, or extremity; the upper side or surface; summit; apex; vertex; cover; lid; as, the top of a spire; the top of a house; the top of a mountain; the top of the ground.</description></item><item><title>Gabriel Casseus Net Worth 2024, Age, Height, Bio, Birthday, Wiki!</title><link>/gabriel-casseus.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/gabriel-casseus.html</guid><description>Explore Gabriel Casseus net worth, age, height, bio, birthday, wiki, and salary! In this article, we will discover how old is Gabriel Casseus? Who is Gabriel Casseus dating now &amp;amp; how much money does Gabriel Casseus have? Gabriel Casseus Biography Gabriel Casseus is one of the most popular and richest Actor who was born on April 28, 1972 in Roosevelt, United States. As Gabriel Casseus tells the story, he could have been a Cosby kid.</description></item><item><title>Big Sean Net Worth, Career and Family</title><link>/big-sean-net-worth.html</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/big-sean-net-worth.html</guid><description>This article is discussing Big Sean net worth, his life, and his career. Sean is an American rapper, singer, and songwriter.
It talks about his early life, how he got started in music, his successful albums, his collaborations with other artists, and his clothing company called Aura Gold.
The article also mentions his personal life, relationships, legal issues, and net worth which is estimated to be $35 million as of 2023.</description></item><item><title>How to Watch Robin Williams Movies in Order Robin Williams Film Facts and Cast</title><link>/robin-williams-movies-in-order.html</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/robin-williams-movies-in-order.html</guid><description>Robin Williams was a legendary actor who left an indelible mark on the world of cinema. Known for his unmatched talent and infectious energy, Williams had a diverse filmography that showcased his ability to excel in both comedy and drama. From his early days on the hit TV show Mork &amp;amp; Mindy to his Academy Award-winning performances, Williams captivated audiences with his unique blend of humor and emotion.
Are you curious about how to watch Robin Williams movies in order and explore his remarkable filmography?</description></item><item><title>Female minded by a shepherd</title><link>/female-minded-by-a-shepherd-html.html</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/female-minded-by-a-shepherd-html.html</guid><description>Crosswords with Friends July 25 2020 Female minded by a shepherd General knowledge plays a crucial role in solving crosswords, especially the Female minded by a shepherd crossword clue&amp;nbsp;which has appeared on July 25 2020 Crosswords with Friends&amp;nbsp;puzzle. The answer we have shared for Female minded by a shepherd has a total of 3 letters but also has other possible answers listed below the main one. Clues often reference historical events, famous personalities, geographical locations, scientific terms, and popular culture.</description></item><item><title>Cam Akers- Wiki, Age, Height, Net Worth, Girlfriend, Ethnicity</title><link>/cam-akers.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/cam-akers.html</guid><description>Cam Akers is a football player from the United States. Cam Akers is a running back with the Los Angeles Rams, who are presently participating in Super Bowl LVI 2022. He has a total of 628 rushing yards and 133 receiving yards.
Quick FactsReal NameCam AkersNick NameCamDate Of BirthJune 02, 1999Age23 years oldBirthplaceJackson, Mississippi, United StatesNationalityAmericanProfessionFootballerHeight5 feet 10 inchesWeight93 kgHair ColorBlackEye colorDark BrownNet Worth$1 millionCam Akers Age &amp;amp; Early LifeHis birthday is June 22, 1999, and he was born in Jackson, Mississippi, USA.</description></item><item><title>Charlie Blythe: A TikTok Star, Musician, and songwriter</title><link>/charlie-blythe.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/charlie-blythe.html</guid><description>Who is Charlie Blythe? A well-known woman on TikTok named&amp;nbsp;Charlie Blythe&amp;nbsp;is also a pop musician, songwriter, and producer.
Charlie Blythe&amp;nbsp;is a straightforward, decent, and kind person who has recently been running in her 20s.
However, she is well-known for her viral TikTok videos, and one independently composed and produced a music album called “Toothache.”
Do you want to explore more about&amp;nbsp;Charlie Blythe?
Keep scrolling the page to learn about the TikTok star Charlie Blythe and her personal life.</description></item><item><title>Onesie fastener</title><link>/onesie-fastener-html.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/onesie-fastener-html.html</guid><description>• To break at once; to break short, as substances that are brittle. • To strike, to hit, or to shut, with a sharp sound. • To bite or seize suddenly, especially with the teeth. • To break upon suddenly with sharp, angry words; to treat snappishly; -- usually with up. • To crack; to cause to make a sharp, cracking noise; as, to snap a whip.</description></item><item><title>iZombie costar who voiced The Origin in the Fortnite video game series: 2 wds.</title><link>/izombie-costar-who-voiced-the-origin-in-the-fortnite-video-game-series-2-wds-html.html</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/izombie-costar-who-voiced-the-origin-in-the-fortnite-video-game-series-2-wds-html.html</guid><description>Crosswords with Friends January 22 2023 iZombie costar who voiced The Origin in the Fortnite video game series: 2 wds. General knowledge plays a crucial role in solving crosswords, especially the iZombie costar who voiced The Origin in the Fortnite video game series: 2 wds. crossword clue&amp;nbsp;which has appeared on January 22 2023 Crosswords with Friends&amp;nbsp;puzzle. The answer we have shared for iZombie costar who voiced The Origin in the Fortnite video game series: 2 wds.</description></item><item><title>John T. Melick Net Worth, Age, Height, Bio, Birthday, Wiki!</title><link>/john-melick.html</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/john-melick.html</guid><description>Explore John T. Melick net worth, age, height, bio, birthday, wiki, and salary! In this article, we will discover how old is John T. Melick? Who is John T. Melick dating now &amp;amp; how much money does John T. Melick have? John T. Melick Biography John T. Melick is one of the most popular and richest TV Actor who was born on June 6, 1959 in Los Angeles, California, United States.</description></item><item><title>Bath &amp;amp; Body Works Brings Back Six of Its Iconic Scents: Details</title><link>/bath-and-body-works-flashback-fragrances-in-stores-201586.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/bath-and-body-works-flashback-fragrances-in-stores-201586.html</guid><description>This one's for all the nostalgia lovers out there. (So basically everyone!)
You know how much you hate it when your favorite beauty products get discontinued? Bath &amp;amp; Body Works understands your struggle. That's why, as part of its #FlashbackFragrance campaign, the popular body shop is bringing back six of its best '90s scents—and they're hitting stores and the web today, June 8!
From now until July 5, you can shop White Tea &amp;amp; Ginger, Country Apple, Plumeria, Pearberry, Juniper Breeze, and Cucumber Melon just how you liked them in your backpack: as fragrance mists, body creams, body lotions, and shower gels.</description></item><item><title>God Loves the World: Preschool</title><link>/96101-html.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/96101-html.html</guid><description>Growing in Grace Curriculum: God Loves the World: Preschool The store will not work correctly in the case when cookies are disabled.
Currency USD - US Dollar "God Loves the World," based on John 3:16, invites children to explore how God expresses love to us and how we should respond. God's love embraces all people in all places, and we find fulfillment in loving all that God loves.</description></item><item><title>Ben Napier Height How Tall is Ben Napier?</title><link>/ben-napier-height.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/ben-napier-height.html</guid><description>Ben Napier, the star of ‘Home Town’, stands at an impressive height of 6 feet 6 inches. According to his wife, Erin Napier’s Instagram post, Ben is physically big, weighing around 300 lbs. His stature often captures the attention of viewers, who admire his tall presence on the show. Ben’s height is a notable characteristic that sets him apart and adds to his on-screen appeal.
Key Takeaways: Ben Napier’s height is 6 feet 6 inches.</description></item><item><title>Who is Dahm Triplets? Wiki, Age, Net Worth, Boyfriend, Dating, Height</title><link>/dahm-triplets.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/dahm-triplets.html</guid><description>Nicole, Erica, and Jaclyn Dahm are famous as the Dahm triplets, who were born on December 12, 1977, in Minneapolis, Minnesota, in that order. They became famous after being featured in the magazine “Playboy.” They also appeared in a number of other projects, including television shows and movies.
Quick FactsFull NameDahm TripletsProfessionActressPopular ForTriplets sisterAge45 years oldDate of BirthDecember 12, 1977Zodiac SignSagittariusBirth PlaceMinneapolis, Minnesota, USAHeight5 feet 8 inchesEye ColorBlueWeight52 kgEstimated net worth$12.</description></item><item><title>Get It Out Of Your Systems, Show Me Your Best &amp;quot;Finger&amp;quot; Jokes! | News, Scores, Highlights, Stats, and</title><link>/34821-get-it-out-of-your-systems-show-me-your-best-finger-jokes.html</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/34821-get-it-out-of-your-systems-show-me-your-best-finger-jokes.html</guid><description>Alright folks, since the Toronto Maple Leafs signed free agent defenseman Jeff Finger, everyone including myself has came up with all sorts of funny and amazing puns.
Immature? Maybe! But Funny? YES!
However, we can’t help ourselves. It’s like an age joke with John McCain, or a dumb blond joke with Paris Hilton. It just has to come out!
So folks, this is your chance to let it all out. Let’s get it all out of our system.</description></item><item><title>Who is Molly McGrath? Age, children, husband, salary, high school, profiles</title><link>/116346-who-molly-mcgrath-age-children-husband-salary-high-school-profiles.html</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/116346-who-molly-mcgrath-age-children-husband-salary-high-school-profiles.html</guid><description>Molly McGrath is an American sports broadcaster and studio host. She works for ESPN as a sideline reporter for the channel's Thursday Night matches, Saturday college football and college basketball. Her love for sports and media started at an early age, and she was actively involved in similar activities throughout her school life. This article takes a deeper look into her career, salary and personal life.
PAY ATTENTION: Click “See First” under the “Following” tab to see Briefly News on your News Feed!</description></item><item><title>Andrea Riseborough Husband: Is She Married To Joe Appel?</title><link>/andrea-riseborough-husband-is-she-married-to-joe-appel.html</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/andrea-riseborough-husband-is-she-married-to-joe-appel.html</guid><description>Andrea Riseborough’s birth name is Andrea Louise Riseborough. Andrea Riseborough is a beautifully and talented presented film actress, whose appearance was so attractive to filmmakers that she was made several offers to participate in their projects. Most often it is TV series or individual shows that Andrea is famous for, which bring moral satisfaction and fame, joy to fans and money to the actress.
Andrea Riseborough date of birth is 20 November 1981 in Newcastle upon Tyne, United Kingdom.</description></item><item><title>Jon Gosselin Says Kate Gosselin Is Not In Contact With Hannah And Collin Reveals When He Spoke T</title><link>/jon-gosselin-says-kate-gosselin-is-not-in-contact-with-hannah-and-collin-reveals-when-he-spoke-to-the-other-6-kids-last-454179.html</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/jon-gosselin-says-kate-gosselin-is-not-in-contact-with-hannah-and-collin-reveals-when-he-spoke-to-the-other-6-kids-last-454179.html</guid><description>It’s no secret that Jon Gosselin has been estranged from six out of his eight children for a long time as he’s mentioned that before. Now, however, the reality TV star got into more detail about the last time he spoke with Cara, Mady, Leah, Alexis, Joel and Aaden and also revealed whether or not his ex wife, Kate Gosselin ever talks to Collin and Hannah, the two kids that live under his roof.</description></item><item><title>1972 Francis Ford Coppola-directed gangster drama starring Marlon Brando and Al Pacino: 2 wds.</title><link>/1972-francis-ford-coppola-directed-gangster-drama-starring-marlon-brando-and-al-pacino-2-wds-html.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/1972-francis-ford-coppola-directed-gangster-drama-starring-marlon-brando-and-al-pacino-2-wds-html.html</guid><description>Crosswords with Friends March 30 2020 1972 Francis Ford Coppola-directed gangster drama starring Marlon Brando and Al Pacino: 2 wds. General knowledge plays a crucial role in solving crosswords, especially the 1972 Francis Ford Coppola-directed gangster drama starring Marlon Brando and Al Pacino: 2 wds. crossword clue&amp;nbsp;which has appeared on March 30 2020 Crosswords with Friends&amp;nbsp;puzzle. The answer we have shared for 1972 Francis Ford Coppola-directed gangster drama starring Marlon Brando and Al Pacino: 2 wds.</description></item><item><title>Chad Kroeger Phone Number, WhatsApp Number Contact Number Mobile</title><link>/chad-kroeger-phone-number.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/chad-kroeger-phone-number.html</guid><description>Author: admin | On:18th Sep, 2023| Comments: 0
Chad Kroeger Phone NumberChad Kroeger Phone Number is +1(579)485-2262. New Chad Kroeger Phone Numbers are given in the table below.
Chad Kroeger is a Canadian musician and singer who is best known as the lead vocalist and guitarist of the rock band Nickelback. He has been the driving force behind the band’s success, having written and co-written many of their hit songs, such as “How You Remind Me” and “Photograph”.</description></item><item><title>Barry Harvey, Dies, 56</title><link>/barry-harvey-dies-56.html</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/barry-harvey-dies-56.html</guid><description>Arrival Artists Angelica Garcia - Ryan Farlow &amp;amp; Erik Selz (USA, Canada, Mexico &amp;amp; South America) Hania Rani - Karl Morse &amp;amp; Ryan Farlow (USA, Canada, Mexico &amp;amp; South America) Mata - Maxx Lesnick (USA) múm - Ryan Farlow (Canada, Mexico, US, South America) Plantoid - John Bongiorno (USA, Canada &amp;amp; Mexico) ncG1vNJzZmiblaGyo77IrbCam5OawLR6wqikaJuRlr%2BktMivnGiakae%2FunnHmqmvnalisaqx0mZsb2c%3D</description></item><item><title>Long Beach Grand Prix cancels Fiesta Friday; Motley Crues Vince Neil to perform Saturday</title><link>/long-beach-grand-prix-cancels-fiesta-friday-motley-crues-vince-neil-to-perform-saturday.html</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/long-beach-grand-prix-cancels-fiesta-friday-motley-crues-vince-neil-to-perform-saturday.html</guid><description>The Acura Grand Prix of Long Beach has tabled the Fiesta Friday concert when the race returns in September, but event officials announced that Motley Crue frontman Vince Neil will headline the Saturday night concert on Sept. 25.
The road race, which typically happens in April, was canceled in 2020 and delayed to September this year due to the coronavirus pandemic.
The Fiesta Friday show has traditionally featured Latin bands. The Friday concert will not happen this year because they could not find a sponsor for the event, according to Chris Esslinger, director of communications for the&amp;nbsp; Grand Prix.</description></item><item><title>Ex-Boxing Champ Tommy Morrison Dies at 44</title><link>/ex-boxing-champ-tommy-morrison-dies-44.html</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/ex-boxing-champ-tommy-morrison-dies-44.html</guid><description>Photo by Bobby Bank Former champion boxer Tommy Morrison, 44, &amp;nbsp;died in hospital Sunday night in Omaha, Neb.
According to the former WBO heavyweight champion’s longtime promoter, Tony Holden, Morrison died at 11:50 p.m. with his wife at his bedside.
The former fighter tested positive for HIV in 1996 at the height of his boxing career. Right before a fight with Arthur Weathers, he got the bad news, which subsequently ended his boxing career.</description></item><item><title>Why was Jimmy not whacked? Celebrity.fm #1 Official Stars, Business &amp;amp; People Network, Wiki,</title><link>/why-was-jimmy-not-whacked.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/why-was-jimmy-not-whacked.html</guid><description>As Batts was a “made” man, he couldn’t be killed without the permission from the boss of the family he was part of (that was, the Gambino crime family), so Jimmy, Tommy, and Henry had to act quick and get rid of the body.
Also, Did Tommy really shoot spider?
Jimmy praised Spider, which angered Tommy, who shot Spider multiple times, killing him. Like many other characters in Goodfellas, Spider is based on a real-life person, and according to the real Henry Hill, his death in the movie happened just as it did in real-life.</description></item><item><title>Daniel Truhitte (Movie Actor) - Age, Birthday, Bio, Facts, Family, Net Worth, Height &amp;amp; More</title><link>/daniel-truhitte-19430910-html.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/daniel-truhitte-19430910-html.html</guid><description>Daniel Lee Truhitte is an American actor best known for his role as Rolfe Gruber, the young Austrian telegraph in The Sound of Music. Truhitte is a singer, actress, dancer and performance teacher.
BornSeptember 10, 1943, Sacramento, CaliforniaYears active1965-presentSpouse(s)Gabriele E Hennig (1966?) (divorced), Mary Michelle Miller (1987?) (divorced), Tarealia Haney (1992-present)Children3Movie Actor Daniel Truhitte was born on September 10, 1943 in California, United States (He's 80 years old now).
He is well recognized for his role as Rolfe Gruber in the classic 1965 film musical The Sound of Music, in which he sang"</description></item><item><title>Disenchanted Is Set To Be Released On Disney +</title><link>/disenchanted-is-set-to-be-released-on-disney.html</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/disenchanted-is-set-to-be-released-on-disney.html</guid><description>The fantasy romantic-comedy musical film Disenchanted is planned to premiere exclusively on Disney + on Friday, November 18, 2022, at 3 a.m. ET/12 a.m. PT. The planned musical is a sequel to 2007 hit Enchanted. The narrative for the new film was developed by a group of highly recognized authors, including J. David Stem, David N. Weiss, and Richard LaGravenese. Disenchanted’s script was written by Brigitte Hales, and the film was directed by acclaimed musical theater artist Adam Shankman.</description></item><item><title>Julio Urias Wife: Who Is Dodgers Ace Married To?</title><link>/julio-urias-wife-instagram.html</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/julio-urias-wife-instagram.html</guid><description>Since Julio Uria is not yet married, there is no information online regarding his wife. Despite not having a wife, Julio Urias has a gorgeous girlfriend named Daisy Perez. The couple has been spotted holding hands and spending time together in public. They enjoy attending dinners and events together. They have also been seen on …
Julio Urias Wife: Who Is Dodgers’ Ace Married To? Read More »
ncG1vNJzZmicn6mwsLnSraaroZWoe6S7zGirmp9fn8Kttc5mrKuhkah6uLXFnmSipqOprqi%2BwKZm</description></item><item><title>LA Times Engaged as gears Crossword Clue Answers with 6 letters</title><link>/la-times-engaged-as-gears-crossword-clue-answers-with-6-letters-1203550.html</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/la-times-engaged-as-gears-crossword-clue-answers-with-6-letters-1203550.html</guid><description>Here's the answer for Engaged as gears LA TImes crossword clue, MESHED is the Answer for Engaged as gears LA Times Crossword Clue. Article continues below advertisement
Article continues below advertisement
Engaged as gears Crossword Clue LA TimesCheck Insomnia option LA Times Crossword Clue here, LA Times will publish daily crosswords for the day. Players who are stuck with the Insomnia option LA Times Crossword Clue can head into this page to know the correct answer.</description></item><item><title>Little pig who's the main character in two 1990s movies</title><link>/little-pig-whos-the-main-character-in-two-1990s-movies-html.html</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/little-pig-whos-the-main-character-in-two-1990s-movies-html.html</guid><description>Crosswords with Friends October 31 2019 Little pig who's the main character in two 1990s movies General knowledge plays a crucial role in solving crosswords, especially the Little pig who's the main character in two 1990s movies crossword clue&amp;nbsp;which has appeared on October 31 2019 Crosswords with Friends&amp;nbsp;puzzle. The answer we have shared for Little pig who's the main character in two 1990s movies has a total of 4 letters but also has other possible answers listed below the main one.</description></item><item><title>Jessica Simpson to Launch Maternity Clothing Line This Fall</title><link>/jessica-simpson-to-launch-maternity-clothing-line-this-fall-2012145.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/jessica-simpson-to-launch-maternity-clothing-line-this-fall-2012145.html</guid><description>With the birth of her first daughter Maxwell Drew, Jessica Simpson opened up a new chapter in her life. The obvious next step for the Jessica Simpson Collection designer, whose empire is reportedly worth nearly $1 billion? An extension into maternity wear!
"I'm so excited to partner with Destination Maternity to design a collection of fashionable styles that make you look and feel great!" Simpson said in a statement released Monday.</description></item><item><title>Magical Engagements for rich-lister, America's Cup sailor</title><link>/magical-engagements-for-rich-lister-americas-cup-sailor.html</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/magical-engagements-for-rich-lister-americas-cup-sailor.html</guid><description>Dominique Wisniewski and Mark Francis had a lavish engagement party.
A rich-lister had his engagement party and an America’s Cup sailor had a magic proposal.
Property mogul Mark Francis and fiancee Dominique Wisniewski had a lavish poolside engagement party at their stylish Herne Bay waterfront home last weekend.
Francis, the high-rolling Augusta Capital managing director, has dated Wisniewski for several years. She runs boutique women and babywear business Lullaby.
The good-looking couple have travelled the world together extensively and turn heads at the A-List events they attend in Auckland in their designer threads.</description></item><item><title>Lions' Jameson Williams Switches Jersey to No. 9; Formerly Matthew Stafford's Number | News, Scores,</title><link>/10044971-lions-jameson-williams-switches-jersey-to-no-9-formerly-matthew-staffords-number.html</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/10044971-lions-jameson-williams-switches-jersey-to-no-9-formerly-matthew-staffords-number.html</guid><description>AP Photo/Paul SancyaDetroit Lions receiver Jameson Williams is yet to play an NFL game, but he has already made a jersey change.
The 2022 No. 12 overall draft pick will now wear No. 9 after getting permission from former quarterback Matthew Stafford:
Eric Woodyard @E_Woodyard&amp;lt;a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Lions?src=hash&amp;amp;amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw"&amp;gt;#Lions&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; rookie Jameson Williams has officially switched his jersey to No. 9 — Matthew Stafford’s old Detroit number. He was looking for a single digit number and actually reached out to Stafford on his own via text as an act of courtesy, according to a source.</description></item><item><title>Saw Gerrera Timeline Explained In Star Wars Jedi: Fallen Order</title><link>/saw-gerrera-lies-deception-gif.html</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/saw-gerrera-lies-deception-gif.html</guid><description>At E3 2019, EA debuted the first gameplay clips from Star Wars Jedi: Fallen Order, and they appeared to be quite enjoyable. The character played by Forest Whitaker in Rogue One: A Star Wars Story, Saw Gerrera, will feature in the game, which is the big takeaway for keen Star Wars fans. What role does …
Saw Gerrera Timeline Explained In Star Wars Jedi: Fallen Order Read More »
ncG1vNJzZmicn6mwsLnSraaroZWoe6S7zGirmp9fqK64ecaeqaudopZ6rbXErGSdnZOavbW1zqdkoKGWZA%3D%3D</description></item><item><title>Nastia Liukin talks Olympics and the #ThatsGold Campaign</title><link>/nastia-liukin-talks-olympics-thatsgold-campaign.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/nastia-liukin-talks-olympics-thatsgold-campaign.html</guid><description>With the 2016 Olympics quickly approaching, athletes from all over the world are preparing to&amp;nbsp;bring back gold for their home countries. &amp;nbsp;From basketball and fencing to football and swimming – Rio is soon to be taken over by champions in a number of sport categories. &amp;nbsp;One woman who knows what it feels like to be an Olympic Champion is Nastia Luikin who is a gold medalist in gymnastics.
Seemingly set to be a gymnast from birth, both parents were champion gymnasts who then became coaches, Nastia was&amp;nbsp;brought up in the gym.</description></item><item><title>New York canal that begins at the Hudson River</title><link>/new-york-canal-that-begins-at-the-hudson-river-html.html</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/new-york-canal-that-begins-at-the-hudson-river-html.html</guid><description>Crosswords with Friends March 2 2020 New York canal that begins at the Hudson River General knowledge plays a crucial role in solving crosswords, especially the New York canal that begins at the Hudson River crossword clue&amp;nbsp;which has appeared on March 2 2020 Crosswords with Friends&amp;nbsp;puzzle. The answer we have shared for New York canal that begins at the Hudson River has a total of 4 letters but also has other possible answers listed below the main one.</description></item><item><title>Salma Hayek in Bathing Suit Wishes You Happy 2022 Celebwell</title><link>/news-salma-hayek-in-bathing-suit-wishes-you-happy-2022.html</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/news-salma-hayek-in-bathing-suit-wishes-you-happy-2022.html</guid><description>Salma Hayek is heating up the new year! The 55-year-old Oscar nominee, and star of Eternals, kicked off 2022 by posing in her swimsuit while vacationing in the tropics. "May this new year bring you the awareness of your own strength. Happy, healthy 2022," she captioned the sultry snap. How does the 55-year-old manage to look half her age? Read on for 8 of Salma Hayek's top tips for staying in shape and the photos that prove they work—and to get beach-ready yourself, don't miss these essential 30 Best-Ever Celebrity Bathing Suit Photos!</description></item><item><title>Norman Fell (TV Actor) - Age, Birthday, Bio, Facts, Family, Net Worth, Height &amp;amp; More</title><link>/norman-fell-19240324-html.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/norman-fell-19240324-html.html</guid><description>Norman Fell is an American film and television actor best known as the owner, Mr. Roper, in the sitcom Three's Company and its spin-off, The Ropers. and his film roles in Ocean's 11, The Graduate and Bullitt. At the beginning of his career, he was introduced as Norman Feld.
BornNorman Noah Feld, March 24, 1924, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, U.S.DiedDecember 14, 1998, Woodland Hills, California, U.S.Resting placeMount Sinai Memorial Park Cemetery in Los AngelesAlma materTemple UniversityOccupationActorYears active1955–1998TelevisionThree's CompanyTV Actor Norman Fell was born on March 24, 1924 in Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, United States (He dies at the age of 74, on December 14, 1998).</description></item><item><title>Amaka Okafor Age: Who is She? Wikipedia - Everything To Know About The Responder Cast Explored</title><link>/amaka-okafor-age-who-is-she.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/amaka-okafor-age-who-is-she.html</guid><description>Amaka Okafor, who will play DI Deborah Barnes in the television series The Responder, does not yet have a Wikipedia page dedicated to her.
The series, with its intriguing plot, contains a lot of drama, thriller, drug dealing, and death, and Amaka plays an important role in it.
Although the characters are fictional, the series is written by a former police officer, Tony Schumacher, and contains many intriguing and fascinating scenes as well as the struggles of a police officer in real life.</description></item><item><title>The Reason The University Of Nebraska Altered Their Mascot</title><link>/the-reason-the-university-of-nebraska-altered-their-mascot.html</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/the-reason-the-university-of-nebraska-altered-their-mascot.html</guid><description>This, of course, was never Nebraska’s (or Herbie’s) intent. “That hand gesture could, in some circles, represent something that does not represent what Nebraska athletics is about,” said Lonna Henrichs, the Nebraska athletic department’s licensing and branding director. “We just didn’t even want to be associated with portraying anything that somebody might think, you know, that it means white power,” per The Hill.
When Henrichs was informed of this newer meaning, she responded by asking the department to change Herbie’s hand gestures to a “No.</description></item><item><title>Beth Winslet - Net Worth, Age, Height, Birthday, Bio, Wiki!</title><link>/beth-winslet.html</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/beth-winslet.html</guid><description>Explore Beth Winslet net worth, age, height, bio, birthday, wiki, and salary! Actress and sister of acclaimed actress Kate Winslet. She has credits in films such as The Shadow Within, Bodywork, The Hybrid, and Exitz. In this article, we will discover how old is Beth Winslet? Who is Beth Winslet dating now &amp;amp; how much money does Beth Winslet have?
NameBeth WinsletFirst NameBethLast NameWinsletOccupationMovie ActressBirthdayMay 1Birth Year1978Place of BirthEnglandHome TownEnglandBirth CountryUnited KingdomBirth SignTaurusFull/Birth NameParentsRoger Winslet, Sally Bridges-WinsletSiblingsAnna Winslet, Joss Winslet, Kate WinsletSpouseNot KnownChildren(s)George Bryn Mawr Winslet JonesBeth Winslet BiographyBeth Winslet is one of the most popular and richest Movie Actress who was born on May 1, 1978 in England, England, United Kingdom.</description></item><item><title>Sue Tollefsen was one of Britain's oldest mothers in 2008. Now she is 70 and her daughter is 13</title><link>/sue-tollefsen-was-one-of-britains-oldest-mothers-in-2008-now-she-is-70-and-her-daughter-is-13.html</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/sue-tollefsen-was-one-of-britains-oldest-mothers-in-2008-now-she-is-70-and-her-daughter-is-13.html</guid><description>Freya Tollefsen has become accustomed to parrying intrusive questions from strangers about her mother’s age.
‘Sometimes it’s a bit awkward,’ she concedes, ‘because people ask you over and over again “Is this your grandmother?”
‘Once, Mum and I were on holiday in Turkey and a lady said: “It’s very nice of your granny to bring you with her,” and I said: “She’s not my gran. She’s my mum!”’ Freya remembers her indignation.</description></item><item><title>Buddy Boeheim Wiki, Girlfriend, Age, Brother, Family &amp;amp; Facts</title><link>/buddy-boeheim-wiki-family-girlfriend.html</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/buddy-boeheim-wiki-family-girlfriend.html</guid><description>Published Date: 28 Dec, 2021 Updated date: 28 Dec, 2021 By Daniel Roffer Buddy Boeheim is now shining at the Atlantic Coast Conference with one after another remarkable performance. With the encouragement from his father and the Syracuse Orange coach Jim Boeheim, he might be a bigger prospect in the NFL in the future.
Does Buddy Boeheim have a girlfriend? Get to know his wiki which includes his personal life, age, parents, family, and career facts.</description></item><item><title>Loni Anderson: Net Worth, Age, Daughter</title><link>/loni-anderson-net-worth-age-daughter.html</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/loni-anderson-net-worth-age-daughter.html</guid><description>Loni Anderson is a name that many people associate with the golden age of television.
She is an American actress who rose to fame for her role as Jennifer Marlowe, the sexy and smart receptionist on the hit sitcom WKRP in Cincinnati.
Loni also starred in several movies and TV shows and had a tumultuous marriage with actor Burt Reynolds.
In this article, we will take a look at Loni Anderson’s net worth, her current appearance, her age, and her daughter.</description></item><item><title>Celebrity hotspot Hollywood hotel The Standard shuts after 22 years</title><link>/celebrity-hotspot-hollywood-hotel-the-standard-shuts-after-22-years.html</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/celebrity-hotspot-hollywood-hotel-the-standard-shuts-after-22-years.html</guid><description>The original Standard hotel, a beloved celebrity hotspot on the Sunset Strip in West Hollywood, has announced that it is closing today after 22 years in operation.
Opened by hotelier Andre Balazs in 1999, the hotel, its bar, and its restaurant became a favorite haunt for a host of stars including Jennifer Lopez, Uma Thurman, and Leonardo DiCaprio, one of the original investors.
However, celebrity support has dwindled in recent months amid strict restrictions put in place as a result of the coronavirus pandemic, and coupled with an increase in rent, the hotel has been left unable to sustain itself, revealing in a statement that it is now ‘impossible’ to remain open.</description></item><item><title>Ramsey Nasr Height, Weight, Body Measurements, Shoe Size</title><link>/ramsey-nasr.html</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/ramsey-nasr.html</guid><description>Ramsey Nasr is a Dutch Actor and Author. He became popular through his role as Milan – Martin” in the Dutch drama film “In Real Life” and his role as Hendrick Goltzius in the historical film “Goltzius” and the “Pelican Company”.&amp;nbsp;He was Dichter des Vaderlands between January 2009 and January 2013. Nasr was awarded the Louis d’Or in 2019 – the most prestigious Dutch actor’s prize. He’s a polar explorer too.</description></item><item><title>Sophie Turner Reveals Her New Tattoos Are Fake</title><link>/sophie-turner-reveals-new-tattoos-fake.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/sophie-turner-reveals-new-tattoos-fake.html</guid><description>Sophie Turner is most famous for portraying Sansa Stark in the hit TV show Games Of Thrones. As a result, when she was spotted out and about in LA with a wolf tattoo on her arm, fans were left wondering whether it was related to the direwolves from the show.Her other&amp;nbsp;tattoos include a kiss mark on her collarbone and a rose and women in short skirts which accompany the wolf on her arm.</description></item><item><title>11 Amazing Bodies of 13 Reasons Why Stars</title><link>/amazing-bodies-of-13-reasons-why-stars.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/amazing-bodies-of-13-reasons-why-stars.html</guid><description>Welcome to this look into the personal health and wellness routines of the cast from the hit TV series "13 Reasons Why." We explore the diverse approaches these actors take towards maintaining their physical and mental well-being. From Katherine Langford's skincare secrets to Ross Butler's fitness regimen, and Miles Heizer's thoughts on mental health, each section unveils unique strategies these stars employ to stay in top form. Whether it's through diet, exercise, skincare, or mental health practices, these insights provide a fascinating glimpse into the lives of these sensitive actors.</description></item><item><title>Amanda Bynes Goes Back to School at FIDM, Parents Are &amp;quot;So Proud&amp;quot;</title><link>/amanda-bynes-goes-back-to-school-at-fidm-parents-are-so-proud-20151210.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/amanda-bynes-goes-back-to-school-at-fidm-parents-are-so-proud-20151210.html</guid><description>Amanda Bynes is once again pursuing her dream of a career in fashion. After some time off in recent months, the former child star is back in school at the Fashion Institute of Design &amp;amp; Merchandising (FIDM), her parents' lawyer Tamar Arminak confirms to Us Weekly.&amp;nbsp;
Bynes, 29, first enrolled at the school in early 2014 but stopped attending classes that fall, shortly before she was placed under a psychiatric hold for several weeks.</description></item><item><title>Dylan Schneider releases music video for 'No Problem'</title><link>/dylan-schneider-no-problem.html</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/dylan-schneider-no-problem.html</guid><description>Country artist Dylan Schneider has released the music video for his current single, ‘No Problem’.
Directed by Emmy Award winner Roman White (Taylor Swift, Justin Bieber, Carrie Underwood), the visual sees Dylan in an abandoned farmhouse surrounded by pictures of him and his on-screen love interest. Throughout the visual, the beautiful girl ‘ghosts’ Dylan by appearing then disappearing, leaving him to struggle with his feelings.
Speaking to&amp;nbsp;Hollywood Life, who premiered the visual, Dylan said: “The inspiration for the ‘No Problem’ music video came to me early on.</description></item><item><title>A Family Portrait Of Hilaria And Alec Baldwins Seven Children</title><link>/a-family-portrait-of-hilaria-and-alec-baldwins-seven-children-534419.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/a-family-portrait-of-hilaria-and-alec-baldwins-seven-children-534419.html</guid><description>Recently, Alec and Hilaria Baldwin shared a family portrait on social media that featured all seven of their children.
Our first picture is with the Baldwin children, the youngest! What a Baldwinito dream team, Hilaria, 38, gushed on Monday on Instagram, making sure to give Alec’s daughter with his ex-wife Kim Basinger a lovely shout-out. “What a Baldwinito dream team!”
Ireland, you are in our thoughts and hearts always and forever.</description></item><item><title>Boban Marjanovic Wife: Everything About Milica Krsti</title><link>/boban-marjanovic-wife.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/boban-marjanovic-wife.html</guid><description>As of 2023, Milica Krstic is 30 years old, while her husband, born on August 15, 1988, in Boljevac, Serbia, is 34, making her four years younger than him.
Milica Krstic’s height Milica’s height is 1.6 meters (5 feet 3 inches), and she weighs 56 kilograms. She possesses a robust physique with natural curves, along with dark brown eyes and black hair.
On the other hand, Boban Marjanovic’s towering height measures 2.</description></item><item><title>How Tall is Trace Adkins? A Guide to the Country Stars Life and Career</title><link>/how-tall-is-trace-adkins-a-guide-to-the-country-stars-life-and-career.html</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/how-tall-is-trace-adkins-a-guide-to-the-country-stars-life-and-career.html</guid><description>If you are a fan of country music, you probably know who Trace Adkins is.
He is a singer, songwriter, actor, and author who has been making hits since the 1990s. But do you know how tall he is?
In this article, we will answer that question and tell you more about his life and career.
How Tall is Trace Adkins? Trace Adkins is one of the tallest country singers ever.</description></item><item><title>Cubs' Bryan LaHair Is This Year's Most Undeserving All-Star | News, Scores, Highlights, Stats, and R</title><link>/1243666-cubs-bryan-lahair-is-this-years-most-undeserving-all-star.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/1243666-cubs-bryan-lahair-is-this-years-most-undeserving-all-star.html</guid><description>The Cubs' Bryan LaHair should be on his knees thanking the faulty system that allowed him to be called an All-Star—a title that he does not deserve.Brian Kersey/Getty ImagesThe 2012 Major League All-Star Game is just around the bend and league rosters were announced earlier today. Like each and every year, there were a few surprises—some players who were snubbed and some who were given an honor that they didn't deserve.</description></item><item><title>Naomi Ross Age, Career, Sibling, Boyfriend, Height, Weight &amp;amp; Net Worth</title><link>/naomi-ross-age-career-sibling-boyfriend-height-weight-net-worth.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/naomi-ross-age-career-sibling-boyfriend-height-weight-net-worth.html</guid><description>Naomi Ross, born on November 1, 1995, is a renowned model, actress, Onlyfans content creator, and entertainer hailing from Florida.
Her striking beauty and online content have earned her significant recognition.
Notably, she is the sister of Adin Ross, a well-known Twitch streamer.
Adin Ross, a 22-year-old content creator, has gained widespread attention for the controversies and content he produces in his new residence, Kick.
Naomi Ross Brother Childhood Tragedy According to sources, Naomi Ross’ younger brother, Adin Ross, was stabbed in his sleep by a mentally unstable relative when he was 12 years old.</description></item><item><title>How do you make instant rice into sticky rice?</title><link>/how-do-you-make-instant-rice-into-sticky-rice.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/how-do-you-make-instant-rice-into-sticky-rice.html</guid><description>How to Make Sticky Rice in the Instant Pot / Pressure Cooker
Soak rice in water for 4 to 10 hours. Add 1 cup water to the bowl of the Instant Pot/pressure cooker. Using a colander that will fit inside the bowl of the Instant Pot (and is approved for use under pressure), drain the soaked rice. Can u make sticky rice with regular rice? To make sticky rice using regular rice, let the rice soak in water for at least 30 minutes before you cook it, which will help make it stickier in the end.</description></item><item><title>Mandy Moore Height, Weight, Net Worth, Age, Birthday, Wikipedia, Who, Nationality, Biography</title><link>/mandy-moore-height-weight-net-worth-age-birthday-wikipedia-who-nationality-biography.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/mandy-moore-height-weight-net-worth-age-birthday-wikipedia-who-nationality-biography.html</guid><description>Mandy Moore is a notable American vocalist, entertainer, and lyricist. She rose to noticeable quality with her presentation single, “Treats.” ‘So Real,’ her introduction collection, was delivered in 1999. Moore has six studio collections shockingly. She likewise has 12 singles, 14 music recordings, three arrangement collections, two video collections, and 18 soundtrack collections shockingly.
Mandy Moore Biography Amanda Leigh “Mandy” Moore was born in Nashua, New Hampshire, on April 10, 1984, to Donald Moore and Stacy Moore.</description></item><item><title>Did Jack Edwards Have A Stroke? Health Update 2023</title><link>/jack-edwards.html</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/jack-edwards.html</guid><description>CelebCritics.com is an entertainment website that tells you everything you know about your favorite celebrity, lifestyle, and news.
ncG1vNJzZmiblaGyo6%2FRoquim6NjsLC5jq2YoGealrCsecSdrpqqlKh8</description></item><item><title>Brooke Sorenson - Bio, Age, Net Worth, Height, In Relation, Nationality, Body Measurement, Career</title><link>/brooke-sorenson.html</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/brooke-sorenson.html</guid><description>Brooke Sorenson is an American Television Actress and a Writer. Brooke Sorenson is best known for her role as Stephanie on the Disney XD series ‘Mighty Med’.Early Life and ChildhoodBrooke’s birth name is Brooklyn Nicole Sorenson. She first opened her eyes on July 13, 1999, in Charlotte, North Carolina, USA. As of 2020, she is 21 years old. Her mother’s name is Stephanie Sorenson and her father’s name is Stephen Sorenson.</description></item><item><title>The 4 Best Opponents for Max Holloway After UFC 300 Win | News, Scores, Highlights, Stats, and Rumor</title><link>/10116897-the-4-best-opponents-for-max-holloway-after-ufc-300-win.html</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/10116897-the-4-best-opponents-for-max-holloway-after-ufc-300-win.html</guid><description>Shortly after UFC 300, it was announced that Conor McGregor will finally return to the Octagon at UFC 303 on June 29, where he will take on Michael Chandler at welterweight.
Despite his long absence, the Irishman remains the biggest star in MMA. However, it's hard to imagine him winning a belt again, even if he gets by Chandler. Instead, he seems to have entered the phase of his career where he will be taking legacy fights—against the biggest possible names, with the most possible buzz.</description></item><item><title>EXCLUSIVE: Interview With Draper - CelebMix</title><link>/exclusive-interview-with-draper.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/exclusive-interview-with-draper.html</guid><description>Emerging UK producer Draper is back with his latest banger ‘On and Off’ which features July Jones and is a&amp;nbsp;powerful and uplifting song that demonstrates the rising star’s artful production with tropical pop lyricism. The new single comes after the release of his second EP ‘Socha’ which dropped back in January.
Since his debut&amp;nbsp;Draper has become one of the most in-demand production and writing talents and has worked with superstars such as Bring Me the Horizon and Rita Ora, and has gone on to embark on projects with the likes of Itch, Twin Atlantic and in particular Låpsley – writing and producing her cult hit single “Falling Short”.</description></item><item><title>Who Wrote The Bible? This Is What The Actual Historical Evidence Says</title><link>/who-wrote-the-bible.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/who-wrote-the-bible.html</guid><description>Though believers say that the prophet Moses, Paul the Apostle, and God Himself are the main authors who wrote the Bible, the historical evidence is more complicated.Given its immense reach and cultural influence, it’s a bit surprising how little we really know about the Bible’s origins. In other words, when was the Bible written and who wrote the Bible? Of all the mysteries surrounding this holy book, that last one may be the most fascinating.</description></item><item><title>Molly McGrath - Bio, Age, Net Worth, Married, Nationality, Facts</title><link>/molly-mcgrath.html</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/molly-mcgrath.html</guid><description>Molly McGrath is a famous American sportscaster, who is renowned for her reporting technique. Molly McGrath mainly reports on ESPN for college games such as Football and basketball. Many people love the way she speaks and makes everything more curious and interesting.Early LifeMolly McGrath was born in San Francisco, California, USA on June 6, 1989. She is 33 years old. Molly McGrath was born to her mother Deborah McGrath and her father Michael McGrath.</description></item><item><title>Universal This is fine Crossword Clue</title><link>/universal-this-is-fine-crossword-clue-1230785.html</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/universal-this-is-fine-crossword-clue-1230785.html</guid><description>We have 1 Possible solution with 6 letters for This is fine Crossword Clue Universal and the Answer is ITLLDO for the clue of This is fine Universal Crossword Puzzle. Article continues below advertisement
Article continues below advertisement
This is fine CrosswordCheck This is fine Crossword Clue here, Universal will publish daily crosswords for the day. Players who are stuck with the This is fine Crossword Clue can head into this page to know the correct answer.</description></item><item><title>Will &amp;amp; Grace On-Set Feud Leads To Megan Mullally Missing Two Episodes In The Final Season</title><link>/will-grace-on-set-feud-leads-to-megan-mullally-missing-two-episodes-in-the-final-season-334882.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/will-grace-on-set-feud-leads-to-megan-mullally-missing-two-episodes-in-the-final-season-334882.html</guid><description>The third and final season of the Will &amp;amp; Grace revival just premiered. But, it looks like an ongoing feud between stars Debra Messing (Grace Adler) and Megan Mullally (Karen Walker) has led to a major disruption in the final season’s production.
According to TVLine, Mullally recently took a temporary leave of absence from filming the final season of Will &amp;amp; Grace, and she will not appear in two of the final 18 episodes.</description></item><item><title>What Is American Football Quarterback Ben Roethlisberger Doing Now In 2022?</title><link>/ben-roethlisberger-now.html</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/ben-roethlisberger-now.html</guid><description>This is the first year the Pittsburgh Steelers have played without Ben Roethlisberger since his debut in 2004. The club’s great’s career came to an end in the 2021–22 campaign.
In honour of the 40-year-final old’s NFL season, a farewell tour was organised. In a video he posted on social media, Roethlisberger made clear what has become apparent in the final days of the 2021 campaign.
“The journey has been incredible, fueled by a competitive spirit.</description></item><item><title>2004-2010 TV show that involved the Dharma Initiative</title><link>/2004-2010-tv-show-that-involved-the-dharma-initiative-html.html</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/2004-2010-tv-show-that-involved-the-dharma-initiative-html.html</guid><description>• Parted with unwillingly or unintentionally; not to be found; missing; as, a lost book or sheep. • Parted with; no longer held or possessed; as, a lost limb; lost honor. • Not employed or enjoyed; thrown away; employed ineffectually; wasted; squandered; as, a lost day; a lost opportunity or benefit. • Having wandered from, or unable to find, the way; bewildered; perplexed; as, a child lost in the woods; a stranger lost in London.</description></item><item><title>See '90s Teen Idol Devon Sawa Now at 43 Best Life</title><link>/devon-sawa-now-news.html</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/devon-sawa-now-news.html</guid><description>If you were coming of age in the 1990s, there's a strong chance that one of your first celebrity crushes was Devon Sawa. The young actor's roles in Casper, Little Giants, Now and Then, Idle Hands, and, later, Final Destination cemented his teen heartthrob status. But his popularity also led him to rebel in order to break away from it all. Speaking of his career slowdown in the late '00s, Sawa told The Independent in 2022, "</description></item><item><title>Jordin Sparks Gets Sexy in New Instagram-Themed &amp;quot;Double Tap&amp;quot; Video</title><link>/jordin-sparks-gets-sexy-in-new-instagram-themed-double-tap-video-2015113.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/jordin-sparks-gets-sexy-in-new-instagram-themed-double-tap-video-2015113.html</guid><description>Better after breakup! Jordin Sparks is embracing the single life in a major way, reinventing herself as a sultry sex symbol in her new music video.
The American Idol alum, 25, debuted “Double Tap” on Wednesday, March 11. The track is Sparks’ first single since her talked-about split from longtime love Jason Derulo this past September.&amp;nbsp;
Sparks is clearly back on the market in the steamy new visuals, singing about flirting on Instagram as she traipses around in barely there outfits and gets close to a new leading man.</description></item><item><title>Emma Watson: Most Boys Hated My Super Short Haircut</title><link>/emma-watson-most-boys-hated-my-super-short-haircut-201249.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/emma-watson-most-boys-hated-my-super-short-haircut-201249.html</guid><description>Emma Watson made headlines in October 2010 when she chopped off her long locks, dividing fans and potential boyfriends alike.
Appearing on the October cover of Glamour, the 22-year-old Perks of Being a Wallflower actress opens up about her shocking makeover — and explains why it’s one of the best decisions she’s ever made.
“If I had it my way, I would have just kept it short forever,” she tells the fashion magazine.</description></item><item><title>Teresa Giudice &amp;quot;Begged&amp;quot; Bravo to Not Air Episode Where Joe Calls Her &amp;quot;My Bitch Wife&amp;quot;</title><link>/teresa-giudice-begged-bravo-to-not-air-episode-where-joe-calls-her-my-bitch-wife-2012218.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/teresa-giudice-begged-bravo-to-not-air-episode-where-joe-calls-her-my-bitch-wife-2012218.html</guid><description>Joe Giudice had a lot of explaining to do to his wife Teresa after Sunday's episode of The Real Housewives of New Jersey.
In a new Bravo blog post, the reality star admits that she initially wasn't aware of the ugly insults her husband spewed during a Napa Valley outing in which Joe calls Teresa "my bitch wife" and, most distressing, a "c–t" — getting notified about the on-air tirade shortly before the episode's broadcast.</description></item><item><title>DISCOVER: Chappell Roan and her single 'Good Hurt'</title><link>/discover-chappell-roan-single-good-hurt.html</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/discover-chappell-roan-single-good-hurt.html</guid><description>Every so often, a singer-songwriter comes along who has the ability to captivate you instantly thanks to their heartfelt honesty and stirring vocals. Chappell Roan is the perfect example of this kind of singer-songwriter. At just 19 years old, she is wise beyond her years and sings self-penned songs with utter conviction.
Chappell’s journey began at the age of 12 when she began taking piano lessons. Inspired by the sounds of Fleetwood Mac and Bob Dylan, she taught herself to play by ear.</description></item><item><title>Ryan Fitzpatrick Net Worth: How Rich Is He? Earning And NFL Journey</title><link>/page.html</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/page.html</guid><description>Ryan Fitzpatrick is the former NFL quarterback who played 17 seasons. He is expected to have a net worth of $30 million as of 2024. He has started gam
Read MorencG1vNJzZmiamaS0s63PobCgoaOpe6S7zGinmp%2BVZIB6f44%3D</description></item><item><title>Leslie Easterbrook Net Worth, Age, Height, Bio, Birthday, Wiki!</title><link>/leslie-easterbrook.html</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/leslie-easterbrook.html</guid><description>Explore Leslie Easterbrook net worth, age, height, bio, birthday, wiki, and salary! In this article, we will discover how old is Leslie Easterbrook? Who is Leslie Easterbrook dating now &amp;amp; how much money does Leslie Easterbrook have? Leslie Easterbrook Biography Leslie Easterbrook is one of the most popular and richest TV Actress who was born on July 29, 1949 in Los Angeles, California, United States. American actress who has appeared on more than 300 episodes of different television shows.</description></item><item><title>This Video Featuring Porsha Williams And Her Boo Have Fans Laughing Check Out What Theyre Doi</title><link>/this-video-featuring-porsha-williams-and-her-boo-have-fans-laughing-check-out-what-theyre-doing-in-the-club-488374.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/this-video-featuring-porsha-williams-and-her-boo-have-fans-laughing-check-out-what-theyre-doing-in-the-club-488374.html</guid><description>Porsha Williams and her boo are having the time of their life. Check out the video that she dropped on social media.
Someone said: ‘Now clean it up and get the hell out,’ and another follower posted this: ‘they would’ve been kicked out …. who thought that was funny ?’
View this post on Instagram
A post shared by The Shade Room (@theshaderoom)
A follower said: ‘aint no way Porsha is is physically attracted to this man and that poor waitress looks annoyed,’ and someone else posted this: ‘What a waste of fcking paper towel😒’</description></item><item><title>Classic boxing combination: Hyph.</title><link>/classic-boxing-combination-hyph-html.html</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/classic-boxing-combination-hyph-html.html</guid><description>Crosswords with Friends August 3 2022 Classic boxing combination: Hyph. General knowledge plays a crucial role in solving crosswords, especially the Classic boxing combination: Hyph. crossword clue&amp;nbsp;which has appeared on August 3 2022 Crosswords with Friends&amp;nbsp;puzzle. The answer we have shared for Classic boxing combination: Hyph. has a total of 6 letters but also has other possible answers listed below the main one. Clues often reference historical events, famous personalities, geographical locations, scientific terms, and popular culture.</description></item><item><title>NBA Rumors: Lakers Still Eye Drafting Bronny Despite Not Being a Priority for LeBron | News, Scores,</title><link>/10120578-nba-rumors-lakers-still-eye-drafting-bronny-despite-not-being-a-priority-for-lebron.html</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/10120578-nba-rumors-lakers-still-eye-drafting-bronny-despite-not-being-a-priority-for-lebron.html</guid><description>David Becker/Getty ImagesThe Los Angeles Lakers are reportedly interested in drafting Bronny James in the 2024 NBA draft as they look to entice LeBron James into staying with the team.
"They do have interest in bringing Bronny James in as a draft pick," Shams Charania of The Athletic and Stadium said Friday on The Pat McAfee Show.
Pat McAfee @PatMcAfeeShow"LeBron James want to play up to two more seasons &amp;amp;amp; obviously the Lakers want to bring him back.</description></item><item><title>2023 Hyundai Ioniq 5 All Prices, Top Speed, 0-60 mph And Specifications</title><link>/2023-hyundai-ioniq-5-hyundais-statement-of-exciting-ev-future.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/2023-hyundai-ioniq-5-hyundais-statement-of-exciting-ev-future.html</guid><description>2023 Hyundai Ioniq 5 is a mix of a little bit of 1980s eight-bit styling and some drastically impressive new-era electrification. The Ioniq 5 sparkles as a fast-charging SUV with remarkable driving range. The lineup houses a 168-hp, single-motor, rear-wheel-drive with an EPA estimate of 220 miles range; up to a 320-hp, all-wheel-drive, dual-motor set up with an estimated 266 miles of range. While the big-range, single-motor, rear-drive model with 303 miles is among the longest-driving EVs sold today for just under $60,000.</description></item><item><title>Angelica Actress Medina El Aidi-Azouni From Netflix Movie Cuties</title><link>/angelica-medina-el-aidi-azouni-cuties-5-facts.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/angelica-medina-el-aidi-azouni-cuties-5-facts.html</guid><description>Medina El Aidi-Azouni is one of four actresses selected to play the leading characters in the French movie Cuties / Mignonnes. Her character in the film is Angelica, and the film is set for a release on Netflix this September.
The movie is coming to the small screen worldwide amid some controversy about the material being dealt with in the film. Parental associations worldwide were working hard to cancel the movie due to the film's content.</description></item><item><title>Aliso Viejo neighbors recreate Pirates of the Caribbean ride for Halloween</title><link>/aliso-viejo-neighbors-recreate-pirates-of-the-caribbean-ride-for-halloween.html</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/aliso-viejo-neighbors-recreate-pirates-of-the-caribbean-ride-for-halloween.html</guid><description>In a small cul-du-sac in Aliso Viejo, a pirate ship has run aground.
Smoke and canon fire bellow from of its decks, a storm rages, all an elaborate Halloween display based on The Pirates of the Caribbean ride at Disneyland.
The moon rises over a pirate ship at the home of Mike and Dawn Stanley in their “Pirates of the Caribbean” themed Halloween display on Oak Ridge Circle in Aliso Viejo on Wednesday, October 20, 2021.</description></item><item><title>Eva Marcille Alleges This ANTM Judge Told Her to Fix Her Nose After Winning Cycle 3:</title><link>/eva-marcille-alleges-this-antm-judge-told-her-to-fix-her-nose-after-winning-cycle-3-i-didnt-know-my-nose-was-broke.html</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/eva-marcille-alleges-this-antm-judge-told-her-to-fix-her-nose-after-winning-cycle-3-i-didnt-know-my-nose-was-broke.html</guid><description>Even though she won the third cycle of “America’s Next Top Model,” Eva Marcille was subjected to her share of tough assessments and frank honesty from the show’s judges.
Marcille recalled a particularly unexpected moment of blunt criticism that occurred after she won the show in 2004. She recounted the incident on the most recent episode of her podcast, “The Undressing Room” with Lore’l and Dominique Da Diva.
“When I won Top Model, the first thing I was told outside of Tyra [Banks’] ‘Congratulations,’ Janice Dickinson said, ‘Now you can take your money and get your nose fixed,’” she said.</description></item><item><title>Home of the NCAA's Trojans: Abbr.</title><link>/home-of-the-ncaas-trojans-abbr-html.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/home-of-the-ncaas-trojans-abbr-html.html</guid><description>Crosswords with Friends November 11 2022 Home of the NCAA's Trojans: Abbr. General knowledge plays a crucial role in solving crosswords, especially the Home of the NCAA's Trojans: Abbr. crossword clue&amp;nbsp;which has appeared on November 11 2022 Crosswords with Friends&amp;nbsp;puzzle. The answer we have shared for Home of the NCAA's Trojans: Abbr. has a total of 3 letters but also has other possible answers listed below the main one.</description></item><item><title>Tua Tagovailoa Girlfriend 2022, Age, Height, Wikipedia, Net Worth, Instagram</title><link>/tua-tagovailoa-girlfriend-2022-age-height-wikipedia-net-worth-instagram.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/tua-tagovailoa-girlfriend-2022-age-height-wikipedia-net-worth-instagram.html</guid><description>Tua Tagovailoa is an American football quarterback for the Miami Dolphins in the NFL. He is from Hawaii and played college football in Alabama. During the 11th week of 2021 NFL, against the Ravens Tua injured his middle finger and knee. Due to his injury being in his throwing hand his throws were a little off which could affect his upcoming plays.&amp;nbsp;
On deck, we have gathered some of Tua Tagovailoa wiki facts including updates on his personal details like his age, height, weight, Instagram, dating, girlfriend, partner, parents, family, net worth, and more.</description></item><item><title>Alexander Volkanovski Wife Emma Volkanivski - Does She Have Any Children? Age -How Old Is She?</title><link>/alexander-volkanovski-wife-emma-volkanivski.html</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/alexander-volkanovski-wife-emma-volkanivski.html</guid><description>Alexander Volkanovski Wife Emma Volkanivski – Fans are interested to know about Emma Volkanivski Children. First, who is Alexander Volkanovski? He’s an MMA fighter, and has been married to his lovely wife, Emma Volkanovski, for seven years.
Alexander Volkanovski is a well-known professional mixed martial artist who is currently affiliated with the Ultimate Fighting Championships, a promotion company based in Las Vegas (UFC).
He was also a professional boxer prior to his UFC debut.</description></item><item><title>EXCLUSIVE: Interview with EBEN</title><link>/exclusive-interview-eben-talks-new-music-touring-and-more.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/exclusive-interview-eben-talks-new-music-touring-and-more.html</guid><description>EBEN is hot and fresh in the music industry right now. Dropping singles every other week and currently on tour opening for his lifelong friends, Why Don’t We, EBEN is on the train to becoming the next big thing. EBEN recently released his singles “Next Ex,” and “Nights Like This,” “Past Hundred Days” and is getting ready to release his next single “You The One,” which comes out April 11th. CelebMix had the chance to chat with EBEN before his show in Boston, MA at the Agganis Arena.</description></item><item><title>Voice Contestant RaeLynn Is Engaged to Boyfriend: See Her Ring!</title><link>/voice-contestant-raelynn-engaged-boyfriend-josh-davis-ring-20151310.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/voice-contestant-raelynn-engaged-boyfriend-josh-davis-ring-20151310.html</guid><description>What will Blake Shelton say? Former Voice contestant and country music singer RaeLynn is engaged, the “For a Boy” singer exclusively tells Us Weekly. RaeLynn’s longtime boyfriend, Josh Davis, led her on a scavenger hunt of clues all leading to places important to the couple throughout their relationship before getting down on one knee.&amp;nbsp;
The 24-year-old popped the question at Belmont University in Nashville, Tenn., on Monday, Oct. 12.&amp;nbsp;
“OMG I’m getting married!</description></item><item><title>AMAs worst dressed! Becky G, Kali Uchis, Diplo and more miss mark at the 2021 American Music Awards</title><link>/amas-worst-dressed-becky-g-kali-uchis-diplo-and-more-miss-mark-at-the-2021-american-music-awards.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/amas-worst-dressed-becky-g-kali-uchis-diplo-and-more-miss-mark-at-the-2021-american-music-awards.html</guid><description>&amp;nbsp;Artist of the year:
Ariana Grande
BTS – WINNER
Drake
Olivia Rodrigo
Taylor Swift
The Weeknd
Red-dy for another big win: Taylor Swift is nominated for three including artist of the year
&amp;nbsp;
New artist of the year:
24kGoldn
Giveon
Masked Wolf
Olivia Rodrigo – WINNER
The Kid LAROI
&amp;nbsp;
Collaboration of the year:
24kGoldn ft. iann dior, “Mood”
Bad Bunny &amp;amp; Jhay Cortez, “DÁKITI”
Chris Brown &amp;amp; Young Thug, “Go Crazy”</description></item><item><title>What is Rosie McClelland famous for? Her Age, Family, Boyfriend</title><link>/what-is-rosie-mcclelland-famous-for-her-age-family-boyfriend.html</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/what-is-rosie-mcclelland-famous-for-her-age-family-boyfriend.html</guid><description>Who is Rosie McClelland?British social media star, singer, actress and YouTuber Rosie McClelland, was born under the zodiac sign Virgo on 7 September 2006, in Essex, England. She has only four acting credits, and is perhaps known best for playing Patrol Garda in a 2017 episode of the thriller mini-series “Paula”, which starred Siobhan Cullen, Tom Hughes and Denise Gough, and follows a successful chemistry teacher whose life’s become complicated now that he’s had a one-night stand with a mysterious woman; the mini-series won one of its four award nominations.</description></item><item><title>Womans TikTok Video on Cooking Mopani Worms Goes Viral Clocking 5.3 Million Views, Mzansi Weighs</title><link>/160623-woman-shares-step-by-step-guide-cooking-mopani-worms-video-clocks-65-million-views.html</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/160623-woman-shares-step-by-step-guide-cooking-mopani-worms-video-clocks-65-million-views.html</guid><description>A woman has taken the internet by storm by sharing her step-by-step guide on how to cook mopani wormsThe traditional delicacy, popular in certain African regions, has intrigued food enthusiasts around the worldThe content creator showed peeps a step-by-step guide of how to cook the protein, and the process was way simplerPAY ATTENTION: Briefly News launched a YouTube channel Briefly TV. Subscribe now!
In a remarkable display of culinary expertise, a woman has taken the internet by storm by sharing her step-by-step guide to cooking mopani worms.</description></item><item><title>Santa Clara University law student SUES college over Covid-19 vaccine mandate</title><link>/santa-clara-university-law-student-sues-college-over-covid-19-vaccine-mandate.html</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/santa-clara-university-law-student-sues-college-over-covid-19-vaccine-mandate.html</guid><description>A California law student is taking his school to court and accusing them of preventing him from continuing his education at another college over his refusal to get the Covid-19 vaccine.&amp;nbsp;
Ryan Driggs, who is representing himself in the case, is attempting to transfer from Santa Clara University’s law school, where he is currently enrolled, reports the San Jose Mercury News.&amp;nbsp;
Driggs accuses the school in his lawsuit of preventing him from ‘securing the economic advantages completion of his legal education would bring’ by denying him access to his transcripts.</description></item><item><title>What is the controversy with Blippi? Celebrity.fm #1 Official Stars, Business &amp;amp; People Netwo</title><link>/what-is-the-controversy-with-blippi.html</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/what-is-the-controversy-with-blippi.html</guid><description>While Blippi has certainly made an impression with children all over the globe, he’s come under scrutiny as of late because of his questionable past. In a video that surfaced online, this popular children’s entertainer can be seen participating in inappropriate behaviors, which include defecating on a friend.
Then Is Blippi a billionaire? He is a former US Air Force serviceman. He has an estimated net worth of $20 million. Blippi is a fun educational YouTube channel mainly doing kid friendly content to help them learn colors, shapes, numbers, letters, alphabet and so much more.</description></item><item><title>Andre Roberson girlfriend, Rachel DeMita's Wiki: Height, Boyfriend, Salary</title><link>/andre-roberson-girlfriend-rachel-demitas-wiki-height-boyfriend-salary.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/andre-roberson-girlfriend-rachel-demitas-wiki-height-boyfriend-salary.html</guid><description>Who is Rachel DeMitaBasketball has never been more profitable than today; players with contracts of $30 million and more per year, have only helped other people in sports become richer as well. Rachel DeMita is also involved in basketball, however, she is not a professional player, but rather a sports journalist with a focus on basketball, her first love. She has been featured on ESPN, NBA TV, and many more, but came to prominence after hosting the first-ever TV show broadcast through a video game, NBA 2KTV.</description></item><item><title>Does Queen Elizabeth II Drink Coffee?</title><link>/does-queen-elizabeth-ii-drink-coffee.html</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/does-queen-elizabeth-ii-drink-coffee.html</guid><description>Since becoming Queen of the United Kingdom on February 6, 1952, Elizabeth II has been one of the most famous and influential women in the world. Does the Queen drink coffee?
Queen Elizabeth II is known to prefer Earl Grey tea, provided by the official royal supplier, Twinings. She also enjoys an occasional cocktail and drinks wine with her evening meal but there is no evidence of the Queen drinking coffee.</description></item><item><title>Is Sario Okada a boy or a girl? Sexuality uncertainty and more personal details</title><link>/116813-is-sario-okada-a-boy-a-girl-sexuality-revealed-personal-details.html</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/116813-is-sario-okada-a-boy-a-girl-sexuality-revealed-personal-details.html</guid><description>People question Sario Okada's gender/sexuality because she sometimes dresses like a tomboy. However, since the actress has beautiful feminine features and loves women's fashion, her fans wonder whether they are wrong or right to suspect she is an LGBTQQIP2SAA member. Meanwhile, Sario Okada has never publicly denied or confirmed these highly publicized transgender allegations.
PAY ATTENTION: Follow Briefly News on Twitter and never miss the hottest topics! Find us at @brieflyza!</description></item><item><title>Cops release pic of missing mom Suzanne Morphew's abandoned bike as husband freed on $500k bail</title><link>/cops-release-pic-of-missing-mom-suzanne-morphews-abandoned-bike-as-husband-freed-on-500k-bail.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/cops-release-pic-of-missing-mom-suzanne-morphews-abandoned-bike-as-husband-freed-on-500k-bail.html</guid><description>Murder suspect Barry Morphew grinned for the cameras as he walked out of jail on Monday, with a daughter on each arm, after posting $500,000 bail.
Barry, who is suspected of killing his wife Suzanne who has been missing since Mother’s Day 2020, looked disheveled but happy as he walked to his car after&amp;nbsp;leaving the Chaffee County Probation Department.&amp;nbsp;
He was ordered to wear an ankle monitor ahead of his trial for murder and evidence tampering, which is scheduled for May 2022.</description></item><item><title>Boyz N The Hood Lyrics</title><link>/boyz-n-the-hood-lyrics.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/boyz-n-the-hood-lyrics.html</guid><description>Boyz N the Hood, a groundbreaking track released in 1987, remains a defining anthem of gangsta rap and a testament to the raw talent of its creator, Eazy-E.
As a founding member of N.W.A and a pioneer of West Coast hip-hop, Eazy-E crafted provocative lyrics that vividly depicted the harsh realities of life in South Central Los Angeles.
With gritty storytelling and unflinching honesty, his verses shed light on the systemic injustices, gang violence, and socioeconomic struggles that plagued his community.</description></item><item><title>Who is Caleb Mclaughlins girlfriend? His Net Worth.</title><link>/caleb-mclaughlins-girlfriend-net-worth.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/caleb-mclaughlins-girlfriend-net-worth.html</guid><description>Caleb Mclaughlin is an American television personality and actor. He was born on October 13th, 2001 in Carmel, New York, which makes him just 19. Most fans know him for his work as ‘Lucas Sinclair.’ This came in the science fiction series ‘Stranger Things. It is a show that aired on Netflix.
Additionally, Caleb has also received several praises for his performance in the Broadway musical version of ‘The lion king.</description></item><item><title>Amphibian who greets you with Ribbit! Ribbit</title><link>/amphibian-who-greets-you-with-ribbit-ribbit-html.html</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/amphibian-who-greets-you-with-ribbit-ribbit-html.html</guid><description>Daily Themed Crossword April 11 2024 Amphibian who greets you with Ribbit! Ribbit General knowledge plays a crucial role in solving crosswords, especially the Amphibian who greets you with Ribbit! Ribbit crossword clue&amp;nbsp;which has appeared on April 11 2024 Daily Themed Crossword&amp;nbsp;puzzle. The answer we have shared for Amphibian who greets you with Ribbit! Ribbit has a total of 4 letters but also has other possible answers listed below the main one.</description></item><item><title>Tyreek Hill - Bio, Age, Net Worth, Height, In Relation, Nationality, Body Measurement, Career</title><link>/tyreek-hill.html</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/tyreek-hill.html</guid><description>Tyreek Hill is an American Football Player. Tyreek Hill is a seedy wide receiver and kicks return specialist. He started his NFL career with the Kansas City Chiefs in 2016. Likewise, he was a Pro Bowl selection in each of his first four NFL seasons.Birth Facts and ChildhoodTyreek Hill was born on&amp;nbsp;March 1, 1994,&amp;nbsp;in Pearson, Georgia, USA. He is 28 years old and is under the astrological sign, Pisces. He holds American nationality and his nickname is Cheetah.</description></item><item><title>Real Housewives of Miami's Alexia Echevarria Separates From Husband</title><link>/real-housewives-of-miamis-alexia-echevarria-separates-from-husband-2015155.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/real-housewives-of-miamis-alexia-echevarria-separates-from-husband-2015155.html</guid><description>It’s over. Real Housewives of Miami star Alexia Echevarria and her husband Herman Echevarria have decided to separate after 15 years of marriage, a source close to the Bravo star confirms exclusively to Us Weekly.
According to the insider, the Venue magazine founders have been separated for a few months now, and had been struggling with serious issues for a couple of years.
Despite their differences, the now-exes, who are currently living separately, will continue to run Venue magazine together.</description></item><item><title>Did Jesus Have A Job?</title><link>/did-jesus-have-a-job.html</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/did-jesus-have-a-job.html</guid><description>As Marcus Nodder explains via The Good Book, Jesus is believed to have been about 30 years old when he began his ministry, meaning that he had to have some means of supporting himself (and possibly his family) before embarking on his mission. And as it turns out, the Bible is pretty clear about what that trade was: He was a carpenter. Indeed, as Mark 6 records, at one point Jesus amazed and upset onlookers with his teachings, and they asked themselves how a regular guy like him could know so much.</description></item><item><title>Michael Pratt Wiki: Who Are His Parents? Age And Net Worth Details</title><link>/michael-pratt-wiki-who-are-his-parents-age-and-net-worth-details.html</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/michael-pratt-wiki-who-are-his-parents-age-and-net-worth-details.html</guid><description>Michael Pratt’s age has been investigated as the Tulane Green University quarterback might be the next NFL star. Michael Pratt, a football quarterback, exploded into the NCAA scene and rapidly established himself as one of the greatest freshmen quarterbacks in the nation.
Football quarterback Michael Pratt is now a member of the Tulane Green Wave. His 247 Sports and Rivals ratings are three stars as well. Pratt also led Deerfield Beach to the Florida High School Class 8A Semifinals in 2019.</description></item><item><title>Why does Anne Burrell wear skirts all the time?</title><link>/why-does-anne-burrell-wear-skirts-all-the-time.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/why-does-anne-burrell-wear-skirts-all-the-time.html</guid><description>According to AOL, she made the choice to wear skirts often for several reasons. Burrell said, Itx26#39;s comfortable, itx26#39;s cute, itx26#39;s a way for me to maintain my femininity in a masculine field and itx26#39;s just fun! What a simple but profound statement.
Also Read: How do you make yogurt starter?
Did Anne Burrell get married yet? Celebrity chef Anne Burrell of the Food Network and Stuart Claxton are officially married, and the first set of wedding photos are out.</description></item><item><title>Draco Verta- Wiki, Biography, Age, Height, Net Worth, Parents</title><link>/draco-verta.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/draco-verta.html</guid><description>Draco Verta is an acting prodigy of twelve years old. Danica Mckellar and Mike Verta, his self-made and talented parents, gave birth to him. Its name is a combination of the Latin words for dragon and constellation. His father suggested the name Draco for a young Draco.
Quick FactsNameDraco VertaBirthdaySeptember 7, 2010Age12 years oldGenderMaleHeight1.43mNationalityAmericanProfessionActorParentsDanica Mckellar and Mike VertaMarried/SingleSingleDraco Verta Age, BiographyDraco is 12 years old as of 2023, having been born on September 7, 2010, in Los Angeles, California, USA.</description></item><item><title>Neil Gaiman Net Worth, Age, Height, Bio, Birthday, Wiki!</title><link>/neil-gaiman.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/neil-gaiman.html</guid><description>Explore Neil Gaiman net worth, age, height, bio, birthday, wiki, and salary! In this article, we will discover how old is Neil Gaiman? Who is Neil Gaiman dating now &amp;amp; how much money does Neil Gaiman have? Neil Gaiman Biography Neil Gaiman is one of the most popular and richest Novelist who was born on November 10, 1960 in Portchester, England, United Kingdom. English author, whose most popular works are The Sandman, The Graveyard Book and Coraline.</description></item><item><title>___ of London (historic castle)</title><link>/of-london-historic-castle-html.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/of-london-historic-castle-html.html</guid><description>Crosswords with Friends September 1 2020 ___ of London (historic castle) General knowledge plays a crucial role in solving crosswords, especially the ___ of London (historic castle) crossword clue&amp;nbsp;which has appeared on September 1 2020 Crosswords with Friends&amp;nbsp;puzzle. The answer we have shared for ___ of London (historic castle) has a total of 5 letters but also has other possible answers listed below the main one. Clues often reference historical events, famous personalities, geographical locations, scientific terms, and popular culture.</description></item><item><title>DABABY SPENDS QUALITY TIME WITH HIS DAUGHTER WITH DANILEIGH</title><link>/dababy-spends-quality-time-with-his-daughter-with-danileigh.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/dababy-spends-quality-time-with-his-daughter-with-danileigh.html</guid><description>DaBaby had a rocking good time with his daughter, Velour, this past weekend. The rapper’s little one, who he parents with recording artist DaniLeigh, was all smiles while hanging with her dad and her big sister.
“Beautiful family pictures,” one social media follower said in response to the candids. “DaBaby with da baby,” another supporter shared.
DaBaby and DaniLeigh welcomed their daughter last year. The artists ended their romantic relationship three months after their little one was born in a very public manner.</description></item><item><title>Loadshedding Has People Stuck on Terrifying Ride at Gold Reef City, Video Leaves Mzansi Peeps in Sti</title><link>/146736-loadshedding-people-stuck-terrifying-ride-gold-reef-city-video-leaves-mzansi-peeps-stitches.html</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/146736-loadshedding-people-stuck-terrifying-ride-gold-reef-city-video-leaves-mzansi-peeps-stitches.html</guid><description>Loadshedding had people stuck high in the sky on a terrifying ride at Gold Reef CityA man captured the moment along with some hilarious commentary and the video went viralThe people of Mzansi had a good laugh at the situation and the man’s commentaryLoadshedding is the pits! However, you can be thankful that you were not high up in the sky on a scary ride at Gold Reef City when Eskom decided to cut the power, lol.</description></item><item><title>Country whose capital is Muscat</title><link>/country-whose-capital-is-muscat-html.html</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/country-whose-capital-is-muscat-html.html</guid><description>Crosswords with Friends May 1 2023 Country whose capital is Muscat General knowledge plays a crucial role in solving crosswords, especially the Country whose capital is Muscat crossword clue&amp;nbsp;which has appeared on May 1 2023 Crosswords with Friends&amp;nbsp;puzzle. The answer we have shared for Country whose capital is Muscat has a total of 4 letters but also has other possible answers listed below the main one. Clues often reference historical events, famous personalities, geographical locations, scientific terms, and popular culture.</description></item><item><title>We Need a Waiting to Exhale Moment: Kenya Moores Estranged Husband Marc Daly Demands Stake</title><link>/we-need-a-waiting-to-exhale-moment-fans-are-ready-for-kenya-moore-and-marc-dalys-divorce-to-be-finalized-as-former-couple-heads-to-trial.html</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/we-need-a-waiting-to-exhale-moment-fans-are-ready-for-kenya-moore-and-marc-dalys-divorce-to-be-finalized-as-former-couple-heads-to-trial.html</guid><description>Kenya Moore and Marc Daily are heading to court to hash out the dissolution of their marriage once and for all. The couple has been estranged since they separated in 2019 and share one child, a daughter named Brooklyn Doris Daly. The former Miss USA pageant winner filed for divorce in 2021. An exclusive report from Radar Online claims Moore, 52, filed documents labeling the relationship as “irretrievably broken” and has requested child support from the restaurateur.</description></item><item><title>Britt Robertson: Unveiling Her Personal Life and Career Highlights</title><link>/britt-robertson.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/britt-robertson.html</guid><description>Britt Robertson, a gifted actress renowned for her exceptional performances, has endeared herself to countless admirers.
This article takes a closer look at her personal life, career highlights, and addresses some burning questions about her relationships, age, and family connections.
Who Is Britt Robertson Married To? In 2020, Britt Robertson exchanged vows with actor Graham Rogers.
The journey of love and partnership that this couple has embarked on has garnered significant interest.</description></item><item><title>What Illness Did Hunter Bryant Child Had? What Happened To Him?</title><link>/what-illness-did-hunter-bryant-child-had-what-happened-to-him.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/what-illness-did-hunter-bryant-child-had-what-happened-to-him.html</guid><description>Both cerebral palsy and persistent lung illness affected Hunter Bryant throughout his life. On Facebook, his family had established a group for him that included people who would pray for his continued health and happiness.
He had been battling for his life for a number of years before he finally passed away. On Facebook, many individuals who knew him in person and who had prayed for him over the years have expressed their grief over his passing.</description></item><item><title>Who is Ethan Waters? Florida Fugitive Wanted Arrested</title><link>/who-is-ethan-waters-florida-fugitive-wanted-arrested.html</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/who-is-ethan-waters-florida-fugitive-wanted-arrested.html</guid><description>Recently in the case of Brian Laundrie, police have arrested a fugitive guy named Ethan Waters. More than a month ago, brian laundrie’s missing report has been registered. The police have tried everything to look for brian laundrie but nothing works. Recently the case turned into a new direction. We will look into the matter in more deep further in the article. Let’s start with who is Ethan Waters?
Who is Ethan Waters?</description></item><item><title>Where to watch Coraline right now | Can you watch the anime for free?</title><link>/125510-where-watch-coraline-can-watch-anime-free.html</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/125510-where-watch-coraline-can-watch-anime-free.html</guid><description>Coraline is an animated dark fantasy adventure adapted from Neil Gaiman‘s 2002 children’s novella. The anime tells the story of a young character who recently moved to a new block of flats. Her loving parents are so obsessed with work that they neglect her. She discovers a doorway to a parallel universe called Other World and what follows is a series of misery. The once lonely girl is the only hope for her parents.</description></item><item><title>Brian Cox Explains Why He Turned Down Role in Game of Thrones</title><link>/brian-cox-explains-why-he-turned-down-role-in-game-of-thrones.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/brian-cox-explains-why-he-turned-down-role-in-game-of-thrones.html</guid><description>Brian Cox almost ruled the Seven Kingdoms!
In an excerpt from his upcoming memoir Putting the Rabbit in the Hat, the 75-year-old Succession actor revealed that he was offered a role in Game of Thrones and explained why he turned it down.
Click inside to read more…
“I’m often asked if I was offered a role in Game of Thrones — reason being that every other bugger was — and the answer is, yes, I was supposed to be a king called Robert Baratheon, who apparently died when he was gored by a boar in the first season,” Brian wrote, via GQ.</description></item><item><title>Texas Man Wrongfully Accused of Shoplifting Wants Walmart to Give Him $100M or Unlimited Free Shoppi</title><link>/texas-man-wrongful-accused-of-shoplifting-wants-walmart-to-give-him-100m.html</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/texas-man-wrongful-accused-of-shoplifting-wants-walmart-to-give-him-100m.html</guid><description>A Texas man said he was accused of shoplifting in a Nebraska Walmart by the store’s employees in 2021. He has now personally filed multiple federal complaints against the Fortune 500 company, asking for either $100 million in damages or unlimited shopping for the rest of his life at any location.
He claims the workers at the retail giant violated his civil rights because he was Black, detailing the March 2021 ordeal in two&amp;nbsp;handwritten complaints to the United States District Attorney’s Office for the Western District of Arkansas in Fayetteville.</description></item><item><title>Jerry Seinfeld's Son's Lemonade Stand Shut Down By Police</title><link>/jerry-seinfelds-sons-lemonade-stand-shut-down-by-police-2015288.html</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/jerry-seinfelds-sons-lemonade-stand-shut-down-by-police-2015288.html</guid><description>Jerry Seinfeld is no stranger to grouchy neighbors. And the actor and comedian encountered a real-life Newman situation while in East Hampton, N.Y., on Tuesday, Aug. 18, when his son’s lemonade stand was shut down by cops.
A local paper reported that Seinfeld, 61, was helping his son raise funds for his wife Jessica’s clothing charity Baby Buggy by way of a classic lemonade stand when unhappy neighbors filed complaints to the police.</description></item><item><title>New arcade skins on the wayBattle Boss Malzahar, Brand, and Ziggs</title><link>/new-arcade-skins-battle-boss-malzahar-brand-ziggs-16146.html</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/new-arcade-skins-battle-boss-malzahar-brand-ziggs-16146.html</guid><description>There are three new Battle Bosses on their way to Summoner’s Rift—Brand, Malzahar, and Ziggs are getting their very own arcade-themed skins, according to the latest update to the PBE.
The Arcade skin line is one of League of Legends’ most popular cosmetic sets, and it’s not hard to see why. Between the bright colors, pixel art, and retro sound effects, these skins have always been awesome since they made their debut with Arcade Sona in 2012.</description></item><item><title>Branching out from the center NYT Crossword Clue Answer</title><link>/branching-out-from-the-center-nyt-crossword-clue-answer-1274532.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/branching-out-from-the-center-nyt-crossword-clue-answer-1274532.html</guid><description>Branching out from the center NYT Crossword Clue that we have found 1 exact answer, RADIAL is the Answer for Branching out from the center NYT Crossword. It will help you solve today's New York Times Crossword Puzzles. Branching out from the center Crossword NYTPlayers who are eager to check the answer for Branching out from the center Crossword NYT can stay connected on our page as we have provided the exact answer for today's NYT Crossword.</description></item><item><title>Is She Pregnant? Reddit Story!</title><link>/mimi-ndiweni-weight-gain-pregnant.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/mimi-ndiweni-weight-gain-pregnant.html</guid><description>Mimi Ndiweni has undergone a minor weight gain, and Reddit users wonder if The Witcher's cast is pregnant. Well, no, Mimi Ndiweni is not pregnant, and the exact story behind her weight gain is unknown. However, she doesn't seem overweight to be discussed, and she is in good shape.
The Witcher, a popular supernatural series on Netflix, returned last week after Henry Cavill's character Geralt's frantic departure. Our three major protagonists, Geralt of Rivia (Henry Cavill), Yennefer of Vengerberg (the gorgeous (Anya Chalotra), and Ciri (Elen Riannon), who is played by actress Freya Allan, have come together in the first two seasons.</description></item><item><title>Veteran actor Tsepo Desando becomes latest talent to join The Queen</title><link>/92663-veteran-actor-tsepo-desando-latest-talent-join-the-queen-html.html</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/92663-veteran-actor-tsepo-desando-latest-talent-join-the-queen-html.html</guid><description>- Tsepo Desaando has become the latest big name to join the hit telenovela The Queen
- The experienced thespian boasts a mega 30 years in the entertainment industry
- Speaking to We, Desando shared how the industry has changed over the 3 decades he has been in it
PAY ATTENTION: Click “See First” under the “Following” tab to see We News on your News Feed!
Tsepo Desando has joined the Ferguson Films production, The Queen.</description></item><item><title>Javier Bardem Net Worth Income And Earnigns From His Acting Career</title><link>/javier-bardem-net-worth.html</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/javier-bardem-net-worth.html</guid><description>Born as&amp;nbsp;Javier Angel Encinas Bardem,&amp;nbsp;Javier Bardem is a Spanish actor well-known for his roles in blockbusters and foreign films. He is from a family of actors and has been working on movies since his early days of Spanish cinema.
With his outstanding acting skills, Javier Bardem has won more than 100 accolades, including an Oscar award for Best Performance by a Supporting Role through his work in the movie,&amp;nbsp;No Country for Old Men&amp;nbsp;(2007).</description></item><item><title>Game where N-34 might be called out</title><link>/game-where-n-34-might-be-called-out-html.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/game-where-n-34-might-be-called-out-html.html</guid><description>Crosswords with Friends April 24 2023 Game where N-34 might be called out General knowledge plays a crucial role in solving crosswords, especially the Game where N-34 might be called out crossword clue&amp;nbsp;which has appeared on April 24 2023 Crosswords with Friends&amp;nbsp;puzzle. The answer we have shared for Game where N-34 might be called out has a total of 5 letters but also has other possible answers listed below the main one.</description></item><item><title>Jena Malone Gives Birth to First Child</title><link>/jena-malone-gives-birth-first-child.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/jena-malone-gives-birth-first-child.html</guid><description>Jena Malone just revealed that she has given birth to her first child, and it’s a beautiful baby boy!
The actress announced on Instagram, that she and her boyfriend, Ethan DeLorenzo, have welcomed their first-born son.
Malone wrote,&amp;nbsp;“The best weekend of our lives!!!,” on Instagram. “What an incredible blessing to be chosen by this amazing , kind , gentle and beautiful soul to be his parents. Humbled and in complete awe that we get to experience the most ancient and transcendent love that exists.</description></item><item><title>Paul Telfer Net Worth, Age, Height, Bio, Birthday, Wiki!</title><link>/paul-telfer-actor.html</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/paul-telfer-actor.html</guid><description>Explore Paul Telfer net worth, age, height, bio, birthday, wiki, and salary! In this article, we will discover how old is Paul Telfer? Who is Paul Telfer dating now &amp;amp; how much money does Paul Telfer have? Paul Telfer Biography Paul Telfer is one of the most popular and richest TV Actor who was born on October 30, 1979 in Scotland, United Kingdom. Most famously, for his role as Xander Cook in the NBC soap drama Days of Our Lives, Telfer is also famous for his character on the show as Luke Marwood on Hotel Babylon and for his guest appearances in The Vampire Diaries and NCIS.</description></item><item><title>Top 10 Greta Van Fleet most popular songs</title><link>/greta-van-fleet-most-popular-songs.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/greta-van-fleet-most-popular-songs.html</guid><description>Which are the Greta Van Fleet most popular songs?
Greta Van Fleet has risen rapidly to become one of the world’s most beloved rock and roll bands.
They have unveiled two EPs, “Black Smoke Rising” and “From The Fires,” as well as one LP, “Anthem Of The Peaceful Army.”
Below are Greta Van Fleet’s top ten songs to date.
1. “Highway Tune” The “Highway Tune” was the song that ignited the hype surrounding Greta Van Fleet.</description></item><item><title>Ballet Dancer Performs Hozier's &amp;quot;Take Me to Church&amp;quot; Has Stunning Moves</title><link>/ballet-dancer-hozier-take-me-to-church-stunning-moves-2015112.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/ballet-dancer-hozier-take-me-to-church-stunning-moves-2015112.html</guid><description>Hozier should definitely consider hiring Sergei Polunin for his next music video. The famed Ukrainian ballet dancer released a now-viral clip of his passionate choreography to the breakout artist’s hit “Take Me to Church.”&amp;nbsp;
In the video, Polunin, 25, leaps, spins, and poses within the confines of a giant room while shirtless and wearing skintight, flesh-colored pants.&amp;nbsp;
Polunin, who has been dancing since age 4, was the principal dancer for the British Royal Ballet and is currently the principal dancer with The Stanislavsky Music Theatre in Russia.</description></item><item><title>Who Is Lana Rhoadess Boyfriend or Does She Have a Husband?</title><link>/who-is-lana-rhoades-boyfriend-or-does-she-have-a-husband.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/who-is-lana-rhoades-boyfriend-or-does-she-have-a-husband.html</guid><description>Lana Rhoades does not have a boyfriend or a husband and, therefore, is currently single. However, she has an ex-husband because she was previously married. Her marriage was short-lived and happened when she was only 18.
Lana Rhoades is a 27-year-old American podcaster, social media influencer, and former pornographic film actress born on 6th September 1996 in McHenry, Illinois, United States. Although she first came into public recognition as an adult film actress, she has since shifted from the industry and now established herself as a social media star and model.</description></item><item><title>Inexpensive noodles often eaten by college students</title><link>/inexpensive-noodles-often-eaten-by-college-students-html.html</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/inexpensive-noodles-often-eaten-by-college-students-html.html</guid><description>Crosswords with Friends March 17 2021 Inexpensive noodles often eaten by college students General knowledge plays a crucial role in solving crosswords, especially the Inexpensive noodles often eaten by college students crossword clue&amp;nbsp;which has appeared on March 17 2021 Crosswords with Friends&amp;nbsp;puzzle. The answer we have shared for Inexpensive noodles often eaten by college students has a total of 5 letters but also has other possible answers listed below the main one.</description></item><item><title>Subway map dot for short</title><link>/subway-map-dot-for-short-html.html</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/subway-map-dot-for-short-html.html</guid><description>Daily Themed Crossword March 9 2024 Subway map dot for short General knowledge plays a crucial role in solving crosswords, especially the Subway map dot for short crossword clue&amp;nbsp;which has appeared on March 9 2024 Daily Themed Crossword&amp;nbsp;puzzle. The answer we have shared for Subway map dot for short has a total of 3 letters but also has other possible answers listed below the main one. Clues often reference historical events, famous personalities, geographical locations, scientific terms, and popular culture.</description></item><item><title>Remember Pat Warren, an Anchor and Political Reporter at WJZ</title><link>/pat-warren-wjz-dead.html</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/pat-warren-wjz-dead.html</guid><description>Beloved anchor and political reporter, Pat Warren, has left a lasting impact on the community with her insightful reporting and enduring presence. With a career spanning nearly three decades, Warren established herself as a respected journalist known for her accuracy, conciseness, and unique sense of humor. Her sudden passing has left the TV|CBS Baltimore viewer community in mourning, as condolences and memories pour in. As the family takes time to heal, the community stands ready to offer support and respect their wishes for funeral arrangements.</description></item><item><title>Is Garlock The Destroyer Trans? Sexuality Partner And Gender</title><link>/is-garlock-the-destroyer-trans-sexuality-partner-gender.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/is-garlock-the-destroyer-trans-sexuality-partner-gender.html</guid><description>Is Garlock The Destroyer Trans? Fans have been questioning Garlock’s sexuality. Keep reading to learn about Garlock’s sexuality, boyfriend, and gender.
Blogger and TikTok sensation Garlock The Destroyer is well-known for her beauty makeover videos.
Garlock The Destroyer’s real name is Ali C Lopez.
Unfortunately, after participating in a gossip podcast with other ladies, she has lately been the target of cyberbullying and fat-shaming.
This was a typical instance of internet abuse when Jabba the Hutt’s voice from the Star Wars film was even substituted for hers.</description></item><item><title>$35 Off | Estee Lauder Coupon</title><link>/estee-lauder.html</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/estee-lauder.html</guid><description>This is what a typical coupon from Estee Lauder looks likeTake a look at these special coupons released during the last 365 days.
How much you can savePrepare to find discounts of up to $75 when you use one of our coupon codes at Estee Lauder. However, there may be a minimum spending requirement. For instance, the largest savings coupon in the last twelve months was only valid on purchases bigger than $200.</description></item><item><title>The 12 Best Barbershops in America Best Life</title><link>/best-barbershops-america.html</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/best-barbershops-america.html</guid><description>It's no secret that we're in the midst of a barbershop renaissance. All those fluorescently-lit, linoleum-lined, and Mayberry-like corner joints of last century? They've been replaced with sumptuous man lairs lined with rich wood paneling, leather accents, and walls of books. And those ultra-cool barbers? They won't just cut your hair—they'll pamper you with hot towels and pour you whiskey and turn up Radiohead while you wait.
To celebrate this wonderful trend, we've rounded up the 12 best trendy barbershops across America, so no matter where you're traveling, you're no more than a stone's throw away from the barbershop experience you deserve.</description></item><item><title>Quin gan el Campeonato de repostera de Halloween de Food Network 2021? Celebrity.fm</title><link>/who-won-the-food-network-halloween-baking-championship-2021.html</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/who-won-the-food-network-halloween-baking-championship-2021.html</guid><description>Fue una feroz batalla entre estos tres talentosos panaderos, pero al final, Renée Loranger ganó el premio de $ 25,000 y el título del Campeonato de repostería de Halloween 2021.
Con respecto a esto, ¿dónde puedo ver Halloween Baking Championship 2021?
Halloween Baking Championship, una serie navideña protagonizada, está disponible para transmitir ahora. Míralo en Prime Video, VUDU, Philo, Spectrum TV, Vudu Movie &amp;amp; TV Store, Apple TV, discovery+ | Transmita programas de TV o Food Network GO en su dispositivo Roku.</description></item><item><title>Freight in flight NYT Crossword Clue</title><link>/freight-in-flight-nyt-crossword-clue-1051674.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/freight-in-flight-nyt-crossword-clue-1051674.html</guid><description>Answer for Freight in flight Crossword Clue NYT that we have found 1 exact correct answer for Freight in flight NYT Crossword Clue to help you solve today's NYT Crossword puzzle by J Nandhini | Updated Apr 19, 2023
Source: fresherslive
Freight in flight CrosswordCheck Freight in flight Crossword Clue here NYT will publish daily crosswords for the day. Players who are stuck with the Freight in flight Crossword Clue can head into this page to know the correct answer.</description></item><item><title>Ranking MLB's 30 Pitching Staffs in June | News, Scores, Highlights, Stats, and Rumors</title><link>/10124943-ranking-mlbs-30-pitching-staffs-in-june.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/10124943-ranking-mlbs-30-pitching-staffs-in-june.html</guid><description>Paul SkenesJoe Robbins/Icon Sportswire via Getty Images15. Milwaukee Brewers
Milwaukee's bullpen has received excellent contributions from Trevor Megill and Bryan Hudson, and can look forward to getting All-Star closer Devin Williams back at some point after the All-Star break.
But while the Brewers have made it work to this point, there are serious questions in the starting rotation. Post-Corbin Burnes, Freddy Peralta hasn't pitched like an ace, and he's really the only pitcher the Brewers have with a track record of pitching 130-plus innings consistently.</description></item><item><title>The X Factor 2017: All You Need To Know</title><link>/x-factor-2017-need-know.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/x-factor-2017-need-know.html</guid><description>It’s (nearly) that time of year again! ITV’s annual singing extravaganza and Twitter drama machine The X Factor is just a few weeks away. Its fourteenth series looks to be a mish-mash of familiar faces and fresh formats – here’s all you need to know.
Who’s Judging? Last year’s foursome – stern Simon, drunk Sharon, crazy Nicole and quirky Louis – are all taking their seats on the panel again. It’s notable as it’s the first time since&amp;nbsp;2010&amp;nbsp;that all four judges have stayed the same – and it seems Mr.</description></item><item><title>Julianne Moore: Madonna Was Method-y on Body of Evidence, Didn't Talk</title><link>/julianne-moore-madonna-was-method-y-on-body-of-evidence-didnt-talk-2015221.html</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/julianne-moore-madonna-was-method-y-on-body-of-evidence-didnt-talk-2015221.html</guid><description>Not even Julianne Moore’s charm and down-to-earth personality could help her strike up a friendship with Madonna. The women both starred in Body of Evidence — an oft-mocked erotic thriller from 1993 — but as the Oscar-nominated actress puts it, Madge wanted nothing to do with her while filming.
During Watch What Happens Live, the Still Alice star was asked whether she was scared about slapping Madonna during one of their scenes.</description></item><item><title>Song such as A Whole New World</title><link>/song-such-as-a-whole-new-world-html.html</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/song-such-as-a-whole-new-world-html.html</guid><description>Crosswords with Friends April 6 2024 Song such as A Whole New World General knowledge plays a crucial role in solving crosswords, especially the Song such as A Whole New World crossword clue&amp;nbsp;which has appeared on April 6 2024 Crosswords with Friends&amp;nbsp;puzzle. The answer we have shared for Song such as A Whole New World has a total of 4 letters but also has other possible answers listed below the main one.</description></item><item><title>ZAYN set to Release Book on Life After One Direction in Photos</title><link>/zayn-set-to-release-book-on-life-after-one-direction-in-photos.html</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/zayn-set-to-release-book-on-life-after-one-direction-in-photos.html</guid><description>In 2015, Zayn Malik made waves in the music world when he left One Direction early in their On The Road Again tour. For months, little was heard from the superstar as he rebuilt his mind and body, pinning stress and a machine like system where he had no freedom to be himself as the cause of his departure and sadness. These were understandable reasons as time went on and many long time fans came to terms with his decision and went on to support him in his further endeavors.</description></item><item><title>Treat You Better folk-pop singer who partnered with Justin Bieber on the 2020 top 10 song Monster: 2</title><link>/treat-you-better-folk-pop-singer-who-partnered-with-justin-bieber-on-the-2020-top-10-song-monster-2-wds-html.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/treat-you-better-folk-pop-singer-who-partnered-with-justin-bieber-on-the-2020-top-10-song-monster-2-wds-html.html</guid><description>Crosswords with Friends September 22 2022 Treat You Better folk-pop singer who partnered with Justin Bieber on the 2020 top 10 song Monster: 2 wds. General knowledge plays a crucial role in solving crosswords, especially the Treat You Better folk-pop singer who partnered with Justin Bieber on the 2020 top 10 song Monster: 2 wds. crossword clue&amp;nbsp;which has appeared on September 22 2022 Crosswords with Friends&amp;nbsp;puzzle. The answer we have shared for Treat You Better folk-pop singer who partnered with Justin Bieber on the 2020 top 10 song Monster: 2 wds.</description></item><item><title>Orlando Pirates: Ndabayithethwa Ndlondlos R20K Lobola Rejected by Baby Mamas Family</title><link>/169325-family-reject-cheap-lobola-orlando-pirates-player.html</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/169325-family-reject-cheap-lobola-orlando-pirates-player.html</guid><description>An Orlando Pirates midfielder, Ndabayithethwa Ndlondlo, was shattered when his delegation allegedly came back without his brideIt is said his baby mama's family felt offended by the R20k he put forward from the expected R150k after the couple dated for yearsSocial media users weighed their opinions about the traditional bride price and its effects on marriagesOrlando Pirates' Ndabayithethwa Ndlondlo was allegedly snubbed by his future inlaws when he sent a delegation to return with the mother of his kids, Kgaugelo Gulame.</description></item><item><title>Riordan Powell Car Accident: Fatal Crash Near Broomfield High School Claims Two Lives</title><link>/riordan-powell-car-accident.html</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/riordan-powell-car-accident.html</guid><description>Riordan Powell Car Accident-Tragedy Strikes in Colorado: Fatal Crash Near Broomfield High School Claims Two Lives. Let’s find out more here:&amp;nbsp;cupstograms.net.
Maybe you are interested William Scallon Bicycle Accident, Queen Creek AZ, Casteel High School Student, William Scallon Died in Accident News: Oscar Holder Obituary, What happened? Oscar Holder Has Passed Away, Funeral Details Selwyn Cooper Obituary, Who is Selwyn Cooper? Selwyn Cooper passed away unexpectedly Justin Adamson Missing: 14-Year-Old Justin Adamson Missing in Cape Harbor Sparks Distress as Family Seeks Help in Search Efforts.</description></item><item><title>Is Nicki Minaj a Billionaire? Net Worth Revealed</title><link>/is-nicki-minaj-a-billionaire.html</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/is-nicki-minaj-a-billionaire.html</guid><description>Nicki has had a very successful rap career. Her hit songs have made her incredibly wealthy, but is she a billionaire?
Nicki Minaj is not a billionaire. She is a millionaire and frequently raps about having money, but has not become a billionaire yet.&amp;nbsp;
Nicki’s Net Worth Nicki Minaj’s net worth reached a staggering $100 million in 2020. She may not be a billionaire, but this is still an impressive and unprecedented amount of wealth.</description></item><item><title>Jack Welch Net Worth 2024, Age, Height, Bio, Birthday, Wiki!</title><link>/jack-welch.html</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/jack-welch.html</guid><description>Explore Jack Welch net worth, age, height, bio, birthday, wiki, and salary! In this article, we will discover how old is Jack Welch? Who is Jack Welch dating now &amp;amp; how much money does Jack Welch have? Jack Welch Biography Jack Welch is one of the most popular and richest Entrepreneur who was born on November 19, 1935 in Peabody, Massachusetts, United States. Former chairman and CEO of General Electric from 1981 until 2001.</description></item><item><title>Brief and to the point and not at all long-winded NYT Crossword Clue</title><link>/brief-and-to-the-point-and-not-at-all-long-winded-nyt-crossword-clue-1102594.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/brief-and-to-the-point-and-not-at-all-long-winded-nyt-crossword-clue-1102594.html</guid><description>Brief and to the point and not at all long-winded NYT Crossword Clue that we have found 1 exact correct answer, TERSE is the answer for Things that Yoda and Brief and to the point and not at all long-winded NYT Crossword Clue. Article continues below advertisement
Article continues below advertisement
Brief and to the point and not at all long-winded CrosswordCheck Brief and to the point and not at all long-winded Crossword Clue here, NYT will publish daily crosswords for the day.</description></item><item><title>School District Blames Ethan Crumbley's Family for Shooting</title><link>/school-district-blames-ethan-crumbleys-family-for-shooting.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/school-district-blames-ethan-crumbleys-family-for-shooting.html</guid><description>Jennifer Crumbley, Ethan Crumbley, and James Crumbley appear in mugshots taken by the jail in Oakland County, Mich., in December 2021.
In an effort to avoid civil liability after a mass shooting, Michigan’s Oxford Community Schools on Friday legally blamed alleged murderer Ethan Crumbley and his parents for a November 2021 massacre that left four dead and seven injured.
According to a “notice of non-party fault” filed in federal court, defense lawyers pointed the finger at Crumbley and his parents, James Crumbley and Jennifer Crumbley, in one of several civil lawsuits filed against the district and its staff.</description></item><item><title>BTS: Butter glides to the top of the Billboard Hot 100 chart</title><link>/bts-butter-glides-to-the-top-of-the-billboard-hot-100-chart.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/bts-butter-glides-to-the-top-of-the-billboard-hot-100-chart.html</guid><description>BTS has scored their fourth Number One with the silky smoothButter and once again, made further history.
Butter landed straight to the top spot of the Hot 100 chart, marking their fourth Number One in the USA in just nine months. Butter marks the biggest debut for a single of 2021 thus far, surpassing Olivia Rodrigo’s viral debut hit ‘drivers license.’ Additionally, Butter has become the best-selling digital download of 2021 so far, in just one week.</description></item><item><title>Angry dispute</title><link>/angry-dispute-html.html</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/angry-dispute-html.html</guid><description>• An arrow for a crossbow; -- so named because it commonly had a square head. • Any small square or quadrangular member • A square of glass, esp. when set diagonally. • A small opening in window tracery, of which the cusps, etc., make the form nearly square. • A square or lozenge-shaped paving tile. • A glazier's diamond. • A four-sided cutting tool or chisel having a diamond-shaped end.</description></item><item><title>Danny Way Net Worth, Age, Height, Bio, Birthday, Wiki!</title><link>/danny-way.html</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/danny-way.html</guid><description>Explore Danny Way net worth, age, height, bio, birthday, wiki, and salary! In this article, we will discover how old is Danny Way? Who is Danny Way dating now &amp;amp; how much money does Danny Way have? Danny Way Biography Danny Way is one of the most popular and richest Skateboarder who was born on April 15, 1974 in Portland, Oregon, United States. American skateboarder who went on to become the five time X Games gold medalist.</description></item><item><title>Ella Halikas (TikTok Star) - Age, Birthday, Bio, Facts, Family, Net Worth, Height &amp;amp; More</title><link>/ella-halikas-19970415-html.html</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/ella-halikas-19970415-html.html</guid><description>TikTok Star Ella Halikas was born in Walnut Creek, California, United States on April 15, 1997. She's 26 years old today.
Her TikTok account, ellahalikas, where she broadcasts body-positive, modeling, and comic storytime video, has made her a social media sensation and model. Her supporters have contributed to her gaining over 340,000 Instagram followers. She also works as a curve model for three agencies around the country and has been in Sports Illustrated.</description></item><item><title>I See Nipples: Nene Leakes Fans Call Her Out for Apparently Not Wearing a Bra</title><link>/i-see-nipples-nene-leakes-fans-call-her-out-for-apparently-not-wearing-a-bra.html</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/i-see-nipples-nene-leakes-fans-call-her-out-for-apparently-not-wearing-a-bra.html</guid><description>Nene Leakes clearly isn’t afraid to show a little skin.
The “Real Housewives of Atlanta” mainstay celebrated her youngest son’s 21st birthday while dressing quite comfortably for the occasion. In her photos that she posted to Instagram on Tuesday, the mother of two wore a black spaghetti-strap tank top and loose-fitting Gucci pants. Leakes took several snapshots with her 21-year-old son Brentt Leakes, her husband Gregg Leakes, loved ones, and with her stylist Alvin McQueen.</description></item><item><title>When Is Outer Banks Season 4 Coming Out: Release Date</title><link>/when-is-outer-banks-season-4-coming-out-release-date.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/when-is-outer-banks-season-4-coming-out-release-date.html</guid><description>Netflix officially renewed Outer Banks for a fourth season ahead of the premiere of season 3 on February 23, 2023. The renewal announcement came as no surprise, considering the show’s immense popularity and positive reception from audiences. According to a production list by ProductionWeekly, Outer Banks, season 4 was scheduled to begin filming on May 30th, 2023, and then run through the majority of 2023 with an estimated wrap date of December 15th, 2023.</description></item><item><title>REPORTNicholas Sparks Marriage Was Over Months Before Breakup Announcement</title><link>/slash-and-his-wife-perla-ferrar-separate-after-13-years-of-marriage-48650.html</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/slash-and-his-wife-perla-ferrar-separate-after-13-years-of-marriage-48650.html</guid><description>It seems Nicholas Sparks‘ marriage did not have a storybook ending for quite some time.
On Tuesday, Jan. 6, ‘The Notebook’ author, 49, and his wife, Cathy, announced they were separating after 25 years of marriage. But now, a new report claims the couple’s wedded bliss actually ended several months ago.
According to ‘TMZ,’ Nicholas and Cathy allegedly filed a postmarital agreement stating neither party would seek alimony from the other in their impending breakup (and assumed subsequent divorce) back in August 2014.</description></item><item><title>Jenny Agutter health: Call the Midwife star, 69, on her 'horrible' shingles - symptoms</title><link>/jenny-agutter-health-call-the-midwife-star-69-on-her-horrible-shingles-symptoms.html</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/jenny-agutter-health-call-the-midwife-star-69-on-her-horrible-shingles-symptoms.html</guid><description>The shingles infection is caused by a virus called varicella zoster virus (VZV), the same virus that causes chickenpox. After an individual recovers from chickenpox, the virus lies dormant in their body, which can later be triggered, causing shingles.
For those who have never had chickenpox, coming into contact with someone who has fluid oozing from shingles blisters can cause chickenpox, not shingles. Although that individual could go on to develop shingles in later life.</description></item><item><title>Camila Cabello, Myke Towers, Natti Natasha, &amp;amp; Rauw Alejandro To Perform At Billboard Latin Music Awa</title><link>/camila-cabello-myke-towers-natti-natasha-rauw-alejandro-to-perform-at-billboard-latin-music-awards.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/camila-cabello-myke-towers-natti-natasha-rauw-alejandro-to-perform-at-billboard-latin-music-awards.html</guid><description>The 2021 Billboard Latin Music Awards stage will feature a sensational show with the participation of internationally renowned stars such as Camila Cabello, Christian Nodal, Juanes, Natti Natasha, Prince Royce, Ana Barbara, Carlos Rivera, Myke Towers, Reik, and Rauw Alejandro.
Representing the most popular genres and rhythms in Latin music, they make up the first lineup of confirmed performers at the prestigious awards show.
The awards will coincide with Billboard Latin Music Week, which returns to Miami from September 20-24, 2021, and will host live conversations and performances with superstars like Karol G, Daddy Yankee, Nicky Jam and many more.</description></item><item><title>Britney Spears Raises Suicide Concerns After She Posts Anti Bullying Message With White Bands On Wri</title><link>/britney-spears-raises-suicide-concerns-after-she-posts-anti-bullying-message-with-white-bands-on-wrists-379844.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/britney-spears-raises-suicide-concerns-after-she-posts-anti-bullying-message-with-white-bands-on-wrists-379844.html</guid><description>Britney Spears is once again speaking out to the bullies who continually harass her on her own social media platform, but now some are worried that the bullies have taken things to far. Britney has shared several messages about the cruel comments people leave on her Instagram account, and when she shared a video message about the deadly Coronavirus, some noticed she was wearing white bands on her wrists. While some said they looked like armbands that someone would wear when exercising or working out, others said they looked as if they were bandages on her wrists.</description></item><item><title>Details About Hair, Title, WWE, Reign, Age, Kids</title><link>/bianca-belair-net-worth.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/bianca-belair-net-worth.html</guid><description>Bianca Belair, the accomplished American professional wrestler, has become a standout figure in the wrestling world. With an estimated net worth of $7 million in 2023, she is recognized as one of the industry’s most successful personalities. Belair’s journey began in 2016 in WWE’s NXT brand, where she quickly gained acclaim for her outstanding performances and commanding presence in the ring. She has competed for various championships, including the historic Women’s Royal Rumble match, where she became the second African American wrestler to achieve this milestone.</description></item><item><title>Florida Georgia Line, Jhene Aiko and more to be featured on The Chainsmokers' debut LP</title><link>/florida-georgia-line-jhene-aiko-featured-chainsmokers-debut-lp.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/florida-georgia-line-jhene-aiko-featured-chainsmokers-debut-lp.html</guid><description>We are getting closer to new music from The Chainsmokers.
On Monday, the popular production duo took to social media to share the tracklist for their upcoming album&amp;nbsp;Memories… Do Not Open. The debut record will consist of never-before-heard features from Florida Georgia Line, Jhene Aiko, Emily Warren and French singer Louane.
https://twitter.com/TheChainsmokers/status/841427484063145985
Warren’s name is listed next to not just one, but two tracks, “Don’t Say” and “My Type.” The 24-year-old is also uncredited on the album’s lead single “Paris.</description></item><item><title>Fans Believe Babyface Might Not Have Been the Problem After Anita Baker Allegedly Shows Up Nearly Tw</title><link>/anita-baker-two-hours-late-argues-production.html</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/anita-baker-two-hours-late-argues-production.html</guid><description>Anita Baker has found herself in hot water again after she had another late start to one of her most recent stops on her The Songstress tour.
On Nov. 18 the “Giving You the Best That I Got” singer performed at the Greensboro Coliseum Complex in Greensboro, North Carolina, but not before making fans in attendance wait for it. In a TikTok video taken from the show, a fan said that Baker walked out on stage “almost 2 hours late” before performing her hits.</description></item><item><title>Alex Galchenyuk Apologizes to Coyotes After Arrest; Entered NHL, NHLPA Program | News, Scores, Highl</title><link>/10083138-alex-galchenyuk-apologizes-to-coyotes-after-arrest-entered-nhl-nhlpa-program.html</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/10083138-alex-galchenyuk-apologizes-to-coyotes-after-arrest-entered-nhl-nhlpa-program.html</guid><description>André Ringuette/NHLI via Getty ImagesVeteran forward Alex Galchenyuk is entering the NHL and NHLPA's player assistance program after being arrested last week and subsequently having his contract terminated by the Arizona Coyotes, according to ESPN's Emily Kaplan.
Galchenyuk, who was arrested on July 9 in Scottsdale, Arizona, for a hit and run, also apologized to police for his "deeply disrespectful and despicable behavior," Kaplan added.
He wrote in a letter to the Scottsdale Police Department:</description></item><item><title>Lucie Arnaz Tells Closer, I See the World Through My Dads Eyes</title><link>/lucie-arnaz-tells-closer-i-see-the-world-through-my-dad-s-eyes-44824.html</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/lucie-arnaz-tells-closer-i-see-the-world-through-my-dad-s-eyes-44824.html</guid><description>Lucie Arnaz is flipping over her latest role. Literally! As sassy grandma Berthe in the Tony-winning revival of Pippin, Lucie is wowing audiences with her awesome acrobatics. “I have a trapeze solo in the show, which is pretty cool,” shares Lucie, 63. “It’s kind of amazing that I’m doing this stuff now, especially at my age!”
Related Story: “I Love Lucy Christmas Special” Features Two New Colorized Episodes!
Of course, performing is in Lucie’s blood.</description></item><item><title>Pokimane Thicc Wiki Bio, ethnicity, age, height, dating, boyfriend, wealth</title><link>/pokimane-thicc-wiki-bio-ethnicity-age-height-dating-boyfriend-wealth.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/pokimane-thicc-wiki-bio-ethnicity-age-height-dating-boyfriend-wealth.html</guid><description>Who is Pokimane Thicc? In the modern world, numerous people have emerged onto the scene through unconventional activities; Pokimane is one of them. She is a gamer, and streams her gameplays through one of the most popular streaming service, Twitch, while she is also popular on YouTube, Instagram, and other social networks. She usually streams League of Legends, and has recently started playing Fortnite as well.
So, do you want to find out more about this YouTuber and video gamer, from her childhood years to most recent career endeavors, including her personal life?</description></item><item><title>Sketch comedy show segment</title><link>/sketch-comedy-show-segment-html.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/sketch-comedy-show-segment-html.html</guid><description>Crosswords with Friends August 31 2021 Sketch comedy show segment General knowledge plays a crucial role in solving crosswords, especially the Sketch comedy show segment crossword clue&amp;nbsp;which has appeared on August 31 2021 Crosswords with Friends&amp;nbsp;puzzle. The answer we have shared for Sketch comedy show segment has a total of 4 letters but also has other possible answers listed below the main one. Clues often reference historical events, famous personalities, geographical locations, scientific terms, and popular culture.</description></item><item><title>INTERVIEW: Lucy Spraggan on searching for inner peace, and finding balance.</title><link>/interview-lucy-spraggan-on-searching-for-inner-peace-and-finding-balance.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/interview-lucy-spraggan-on-searching-for-inner-peace-and-finding-balance.html</guid><description>To find both healing and resolution in relinquishing control of past traumas is no mean feat. Nor is simultaneously publishing a book, and releasing an album that recount in great detail the reasons behind, and after effects of, dealing with said trauma – just ask Lucy Spraggan…
“The way I see it, there are two ways to deal with the past – you either embrace it, and learn from it, or you keep running, and remain a prisoner to it for the rest of your life,” a considered, yet good-humoured Lucy muses as we chat just weeks before the launch of her autobiography ‘Process: Finding My Way Through’, and 7th studio album, ‘Balance’.</description></item><item><title>4 WWE and AEW Stars Who Aren't Living Up to the Hype | News, Scores, Highlights, Stats, and Rumors</title><link>/10125813-4-wwe-and-aew-stars-who-arent-living-up-to-the-hype.html</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/10125813-4-wwe-and-aew-stars-who-arent-living-up-to-the-hype.html</guid><description>WWE/Getty ImagesSolo Sikoa is the face of The Bloodline right now and while he has put in the work to develop himself both between the ropes and as an on-screen presence, there is an argument to be made that he was elevated to the position of interim Tribal Chief way before he was ready for it.
The enforcer of the group spent his first year and a half as the silent bodyguard for Roman Reigns, doing his bidding and watching at a distance.</description></item><item><title>Leighton Meester, Adam Brody Welcome Baby Girl, Name Revealed</title><link>/leighton-meester-adam-brody-welcome-baby-girl-name-revealed-2015249.html</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/leighton-meester-adam-brody-welcome-baby-girl-name-revealed-2015249.html</guid><description>Xoxo to this baby girl! New mom Leighton Meester and her husband, Adam Brody, have welcomed a baby girl. The gender was revealed on Thursday, Sept. 24, shortly after Us Weekly broke news that the Gossip Girl alum had given birth.
TMZ obtained the child's birth certificate, revealing that the stars named their newborn baby daughter Arlo Day.
According to the document, Meester, 29, and Brody, 35, secretly welcomed their baby girl in a hospital that wasn't the usual celeb-favored Cedars-Sinai Medical Center.</description></item><item><title>McKinsey partner accused of insider trading in Goldman GreenSky purchase</title><link>/mckinsey-partner-accused-of-insider-trading-in-goldman-greensky-purchase.html</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/mckinsey-partner-accused-of-insider-trading-in-goldman-greensky-purchase.html</guid><description>A partner at the McKinsey consulting firm was criminally charged on Wednesday with insider trading ahead of Goldman Sachs Group Inc’s agreement to buy fintech lender GreenSky Inc for $2.24 billion, U.S. prosecutors said on Wednesday.
Puneet&amp;nbsp;Dikshit, 40, of Manhattan, faces two securities fraud counts after allegedly generating about $450,000 of profit from 2,500 GreenSky call options that he bought in the two days before the merger was announced on Sept.</description></item><item><title>Snoop Dogg Publicly Shows Love And Appreciation To His Wife, Following Fresh Cheating Allegations Ma</title><link>/snoop-dogg-publicly-shows-love-and-appreciation-to-his-wife-following-fresh-cheating-allegations-made-by-the-infamous-celina-powell-393772.html</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/snoop-dogg-publicly-shows-love-and-appreciation-to-his-wife-following-fresh-cheating-allegations-made-by-the-infamous-celina-powell-393772.html</guid><description>Snoop Dogg felt the need to publicly show his wife love and appreciation so he shared an IG post with a message to her. This comes right after the infamous Celina Powel came back online with cheating accusations involving the rapper.
She claimed a while ago that he cheated on his wife with her, and this was a massive scandal back then.
‘@bosslady_ent. Thanks4 the . Kids loyalty stability n the ability to deal with me on my worst days 🥰 u are appreciated 💝💙💯’ Snoop captioned his post.</description></item><item><title>Bo Burnham Height How Tall is the Internet Comedian?</title><link>/bo-burnham-height.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/bo-burnham-height.html</guid><description>Bo Burnham is an American comedian, musician, and filmmaker. He first gained popularity through his comedic music videos on YouTube, which went viral and led to his debut album “Bo Burnham” in 2009.
He has since released several other successful albums, and has also written and directed his own comedy specials and films. He is known for his unique comedic style, which often blends satire, social commentary, and musical performance.</description></item><item><title>Inconsequential</title><link>/inconsequential-html.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/inconsequential-html.html</guid><description>Crosswords with Friends March 31 2022 Inconsequential General knowledge plays a crucial role in solving crosswords, especially the Inconsequential crossword clue&amp;nbsp;which has appeared on March 31 2022 Crosswords with Friends&amp;nbsp;puzzle. The answer we have shared for Inconsequential has a total of 5 letters but also has other possible answers listed below the main one. Clues often reference historical events, famous personalities, geographical locations, scientific terms, and popular culture. This makes crosswords not just a test of one's linguistic abilities but also an exercise in general knowledge and cultural literacy.</description></item><item><title>Significant Mother's Bro Code: Is Sleeping With Your BFF's Mom Okay?</title><link>/significant-mothers-bro-code-is-sleeping-with-your-bffs-mom-okay-201538.html</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/significant-mothers-bro-code-is-sleeping-with-your-bffs-mom-okay-201538.html</guid><description>Is it okay to sleep with your BFF’s mother? That’s what The CW’s new comedy, Significant Mother, asks. Roomies Jimmy (Nathaniel Buzolic) and Nate (Josh Zuckerman) grew up together, but their relationship is tested when Nate comes home from a business trip only to find that his mother and Jimmy have been hooking up behind his back.
“If you picture the most awkward scenario that three people could have, it would be your best friend dating your mom, and that’s what basically happens on our show,” Buzolic explains during a July visit to the Us Weekly offices in Los Angeles.</description></item><item><title>Willow Smith Says She Want Dreads in CR Fashion Book: Photos</title><link>/willow-smith-says-she-want-dreads-in-cr-fashion-book-photos-201543.html</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/willow-smith-says-she-want-dreads-in-cr-fashion-book-photos-201543.html</guid><description>Embracing her style!&amp;nbsp;
Gone are the days of whipping her hair in bubblegum pop videos. Willow Smith brings her eclectic vibe to the new issue of CR Fashion Book&amp;nbsp;(on newsstands March 5) as the muse for L.A. jewelry designer Lisa Eisner. Will Smith and Jada Pinkett Smith’s 14-year-old daughter sports natural bronzy-nude makeup, emerald metallic green nails that resemble sharp claws, and her short hair is worn in its natural textured state with blonde highlights.</description></item><item><title>Mel Sembler</title><link>/mel-sembler.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/mel-sembler.html</guid><description>Learn about Mel Sembler Net Worth, Biography, Age, Birthday, Height, Early Life, Family, Dating, Partner, Wiki, and Facts.
Who is Mel Sembler:Mel Sembler is a famous American diplomat. He was born on May 10, 1930 and his birthplace is St. Joseph Missouri.
On Buzzlearn.com, Mel is listed as a successful Diplomat who was born in the year of 1930. He is also ranked in the richest person list from United States.</description></item><item><title>Sarah Hyland: What's In My Bag?</title><link>/sarah-hyland-wimb-2015199.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/sarah-hyland-wimb-2015199.html</guid><description>Nothing to sneeze at! Sarah Hyland is always prepared for a pollen attack. “I carry tons and tons of tissues because of my bad allergies,” says the star of Modern Family (Season 7 premieres on ABC Sept. 23 at 9 p.m). “I’m like a grandma.” The New York native, 24, who dates British actor Dominic Sherwood, 25, lets Us Weekly nose around her Lady Dior tote.
Less Is More
“I don’t wear a lot of makeup when I’m not at work, but I need my Diorshow Iconic Overcurl mascara.</description></item><item><title>Kelly Clarksons Body Evolution Through the Years</title><link>/kelly-clarksons-body-through-the-years-2012317.html</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/kelly-clarksons-body-through-the-years-2012317.html</guid><description>Comfortable in her skin! Through the years,&amp;nbsp;Kelly Clarkson has been outspoken about body empowerment — and has used her experience to inspire others.
The “Miss Independent” singer previously spoke out aboutbeing publicly criticized for her weight when she skyrocketed to fame during season 1 of the hit competition show. “I was the biggest girl in the [American Idol cast] too,” Clarkson said on The Ellen DeGeneres Show in 2015. “And I wasn’t big, but people would call me big … I’ve kind of always gotten that.</description></item><item><title>Young Womans TikTok Video on Career Choice as a Tech Consultant Trends, Captivates Netizens</title><link>/163661-young-womans-tiktok-video-career-choice-a-tech-consultant-captivates-netizens.html</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/163661-young-womans-tiktok-video-career-choice-a-tech-consultant-captivates-netizens.html</guid><description>A TikTok video posted by a young woman about her career choice as a tech consultant has intrigued netizens The lady shared her passion for technology and explained what she does in the day, which is filled with meetings Netizens have been captivated by her story, expressing their curiosity and admiration for her career pathPAY ATTENTION: Empowering lives, one story at a time. Briefly News launched a YouTube channel Briefly TV.</description></item><item><title>Layla Kiffin Pictures: Lane and His Smokin' Wife Bolt for USC | News, Scores, Highlights, Stats, and</title><link>/325329-layla-kiffin-pics-lane-and-his-smokin-wife-bolt-for-usc.html</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/325329-layla-kiffin-pics-lane-and-his-smokin-wife-bolt-for-usc.html</guid><description>Layla Kiffin Pictures: Lane and His Smokin' Wife Bolt for USC | News, Scores, Highlights, Stats, and Rumors | Bleacher ReportncG1vNJzZmianJqupLTEq6meqJ%2BnwW%2BvzqZmmqqknrCtsdJoamttY2eGbrjAsqOaZZues6e1zWanopujYrmiusRmmKecXZ22tHnSpqakoZ5ixKqyxGaZqKSkYrOwvoyuqpw%3D</description></item><item><title>Portmanteau in 2010s fandom NYT Crossword Answers</title><link>/portmanteau-in-2010s-fandom-nyt-crossword-answers-1174180.html</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/portmanteau-in-2010s-fandom-nyt-crossword-answers-1174180.html</guid><description>Portmanteau in 2010s fandom NYT Crossword Clue that we have found 1 exact answer, BELIEBERS is the Answer for Portmanteau in 2010s fandom NYT Crossword. It will help you solve today's New York Times Crossword Puzzles. Portmanteau in 2010s fandom NYT Crossword ClueThe Portmanteau in 2010s fandom NYT crossword clue is a common type of clue that appears in The New York Times crossword puzzle. This clue often requires solvers to come up with a word or phrase that represents a question or a query.</description></item><item><title>Paige Danielle- Age, Net Worth, Boyfriend, Height, Weight, Religion</title><link>/paige-danielle.html</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/paige-danielle.html</guid><description>Paige Danielle is a YouTube sensation and make-up artist from the United States. Paige Danielle does the make-up and uploads footage on YouTube. Her YouTube channel ‘Paigique’ is well-known. She has exceeded all expectations to become a professional stylist. She brings her fans up to date with fashion and make-up updates daily. In her videos, she shows various looks at various times. She vlogs her everyday life as an enthusiastic ‘vlogger.</description></item><item><title>Troian Bellisario Engaged to Patrick J. Adams: I'm &amp;quot;Loving All Of It&amp;quot;</title><link>/troian-bellisario-engaged-to-patrick-j-adams-im-loving-all-of-it-2014116.html</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/troian-bellisario-engaged-to-patrick-j-adams-im-loving-all-of-it-2014116.html</guid><description>Pretty little engagement! Troian Bellisario and Patrick J. Adams have kept quiet about their impending nuptials since the Suits actor popped the question, but all of that changed on Tuesday, June 10. Bellisario gushed about the couple's next step to Us Weekly while attending the Max Mara Women in Film Cocktails event at the Chateau Marmont in West Hollywood.
It's "not any different. It's bizarre. It's not any different," the 28-year-old told Us.</description></item><item><title>No. 2: Orioles | Highlights and Live Video from Bleacher Report</title><link>/572660-no-2-orioles.html</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/572660-no-2-orioles.html</guid><description>Bleacher ReportBleacher ReportNBANBA RUMORSMLBWNBANFL WWETENNISSPORTSSCORESPLAYSHOPAccount
Bleacher Report LogoFacebook LogoInstagram LogoAboutAdvertiseContact UsGet HelpCareersSitemapCommunity GuidelinesPrivacyDo Not Sell or Share My Personal InformationTerms Of UseAdChoicesB/R Sports on MAXB/R Creators ProgramCopyright © 2024 Bleacher Report, Inc. A Warner Bros. Discovery Company. All Rights Reserved.ncG1vNJzZmianJqupLTEq6meqJ%2BnwW%2BvzqZmr6GUmry0e5RwaW9uYGK7sHmRZqaroZ%2BhsrQ%3D</description></item><item><title>TikTok: A Closer look at Ronald Williamss death and his recent illnesses</title><link>/tiktok-a-closer-look-at-ronald-williamss-death-and-his-recent-illnesses.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/tiktok-a-closer-look-at-ronald-williamss-death-and-his-recent-illnesses.html</guid><description>Sadly, the world’s favorite and perhaps most famous grandpa has passed away months before his 80th birthday. Ronald Williams, also known as Grandpa Lou Pickles due to his resemblance to the famous Rugrats character, launched his social media career via TikTok in February 2020.
In his first video, Williams promised to post regularly, and he delivered on that promise. His most viral clips were videos of himself playing the TikTok game Hit or Miss.</description></item><item><title>What happened? Offense went sour quickly for Hogs</title><link>/offense-went-sour-quickly-for-hogs.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/offense-went-sour-quickly-for-hogs.html</guid><description>What happened? Offense went sour quickly for Hogs: The University of Arkansas Razorbacks are looking to bounce back after a disappointing loss to Auburn, where their offense struggled to find its rhythm. Despite the setback, head coach Sam Pittman remains confident in offensive coordinator Kenny Guiton’s ability to lead the team to success. With star players KJ Jefferson and Raheim Sanders leading the charge, the Razorbacks are determined to rediscover the explosive form they displayed in their victory against Florida.</description></item><item><title>School of whales</title><link>/school-of-whales-html.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/school-of-whales-html.html</guid><description>Daily Themed Crossword January 31 2024 School of whales General knowledge plays a crucial role in solving crosswords, especially the School of whales crossword clue&amp;nbsp;which has appeared on January 31 2024 Daily Themed Crossword&amp;nbsp;puzzle. The answer we have shared for School of whales has a total of 3 letters but also has other possible answers listed below the main one. Clues often reference historical events, famous personalities, geographical locations, scientific terms, and popular culture.</description></item><item><title>The Kanye West Quote that Changed Bruce Jenners Life</title><link>/kanye-west-quote-changed-bruce-jenners-life.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/kanye-west-quote-changed-bruce-jenners-life.html</guid><description>Recently, ABC aired a long-awaited interview between Bruce Jenner and Diane Sawyer, in which Jenner opened up about his personal life and his past. &amp;nbsp;During the interview, Jenner took&amp;nbsp;Sawyer and the rest of the country on a painstaking journey throughout his life as a confused man looking to find the answer to his internal struggle. &amp;nbsp;As many were expecting, Jenner revealed that he is transgender, and is on his way to transitioning into the female he’s always been on the inside.</description></item><item><title>NBC Fall Schedule 2022: 'La Brea,' 'Quantum Leap,' 'The Voice'</title><link>/nbc-fall-schedule-2022-la-brea-quantum-leap-the-voice.html</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/nbc-fall-schedule-2022-la-brea-quantum-leap-the-voice.html</guid><description>NBC revealed its fall 2022-2023 lineup Monday, which includes “La Brea” occupying the current Tuesdays at 9 p.m. home of “This Is Us,” as well as the “Quantum Leap” reboot series taking the coveted post-“The Voice” launchpad. On a season that includes new coach Camila Cabello, that’s an even nicer slot to occupy as the broadcast network’s splashy new drama.
Mondays in the fall will begin with the two-hour episode of “The Voice” at 8, followed by “Quantum Leap” at 10.</description></item><item><title>What Is Shania Twains Real Name? Heres Why She Changed It</title><link>/shania-twain-real-name.html</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/shania-twain-real-name.html</guid><description>A well-known figure in the music business, particularly in the country music genre, is Shania Twain. Even the most ardent critics of country music are familiar with “Man! I Fell Like A Woman!” and “You’re Still The One,” two of her mega-hits. Her huge power move in “That Don’t Impress Me Much,” in which she mentions Brad Pitt and claims that even the A-list actor must have substance in order to meet her standards, is still remembered as a classic karaoke moment.</description></item><item><title>41 Quotes About Being Mistreated In a Relationship</title><link>/41-quotes-mistreated-relationship.html</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/41-quotes-mistreated-relationship.html</guid><description>Suffering through an emotionally abusive relationship is troubling for many. However, it takes a lot of strength and courage to recognize this mistreatment and to take action to rectify it. Here are some great quites about being mistreated in a relationship that capture these types of environments.
“A child that’s being abused by its parents doesn’t stop loving its parents, it stops loving itself.”
“If a normally kind, agreeable person makes an enemy of you, you ought to ask yourself why.</description></item><item><title>Why Did Family Guy Lois Griffin Dead Prank Trend On TikTok? 5 Things About The Family Guy Character</title><link>/why-did-family-guy-lois-griffin-dead-prank-trend-on-tiktok.html</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/why-did-family-guy-lois-griffin-dead-prank-trend-on-tiktok.html</guid><description>Why Did Family Guy Lois Griffin Dead Prank Trend On TikTok? Griffin Lois from Family Guy On December 26, 2022, a dead hoax went viral on Twitter as people posted the responses of their loved ones after telling them that Lois Griffin had passed away at the age of 43.
A made-up character from the animated television sitcom Family Guy is named Lois Patrice Griffin.
She is voiced by Alex Borstein, who first debuted on television with the Griffin family on December 20, 1998, in a 15-minute short.</description></item><item><title>Rush Processing Fee Blessed Celebration</title><link>/rush-processing-fee.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rush-processing-fee.html</guid><description>Blessed Celebration did a great job fulfilling a last minute order for baptismal pins. The pins looks beautiful (white ribbon with gold lettering and a gold colored cross) and they arrived in plenty of time thanks to BC’s rush option. I would definitely order from them again. Side note: I went with the option of ordering the pins with the catechumen’s birth name and I didn’t add the baptismal name. Next time I would add the baptismal name too.</description></item><item><title>Sandra Bullock Sets Her Sights on Finding Mr. Right in 2015 After Years of Heartbreak</title><link>/sandra-bullock-sets-her-sights-on-finding-mr-right-in-2015-after-years-of-heartbreak-49267.html</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/sandra-bullock-sets-her-sights-on-finding-mr-right-in-2015-after-years-of-heartbreak-49267.html</guid><description>Always one to put family first, Oscar-winning actress Sandra Bullock celebrated the holiday season with her son, Louis, 4, on a vacation to Jackson Hole, Wyo., where she enrolled him in ski lessons so they could hit the slopes together. Along with her loving family, Sandra has great friends and a thriving career. Yet one thing’s still missing from the actress. “Sandra has everything a woman could want in life – except a good man,” confides a pal.</description></item><item><title>Tamar Braxtons net worth, age, children, TV shows, songs, career, profiles</title><link>/127600-tamar-braxtons-net-worth-age-children-tv-shows-songs-career-profiles.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/127600-tamar-braxtons-net-worth-age-children-tv-shows-songs-career-profiles.html</guid><description>Is Tamar Braxton rich? This is one of the commonly asked questions about the Braxton sisters, thanks to their success. So, how rich is this songstress? Find out in this read as we decrypt Tamar Braxton's net worth in 2022.
PAY ATTENTION: Click “See First” under the “Following” tab to see Briefly News on your News Feed!
The beauty's music career has faced its fair share of ups and downs.</description></item><item><title>Feeling in many emo songs</title><link>/feeling-in-many-emo-songs-html.html</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/feeling-in-many-emo-songs-html.html</guid><description>Crosswords with Friends December 4 2019 Feeling in many emo songs General knowledge plays a crucial role in solving crosswords, especially the Feeling in many emo songs crossword clue&amp;nbsp;which has appeared on December 4 2019 Crosswords with Friends&amp;nbsp;puzzle. The answer we have shared for Feeling in many emo songs has a total of 5 letters but also has other possible answers listed below the main one. Clues often reference historical events, famous personalities, geographical locations, scientific terms, and popular culture.</description></item><item><title>Cook County ME ID's 3 found dead at James Sneider Apartments in Rogers Park amid hot Chicago weather</title><link>/cook-county-me-ids-3-found-dead-at-james-sneider-apartments-in-rogers-park-amid-hot-chicago-weather-residents-call-for-action.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/cook-county-me-ids-3-found-dead-at-james-sneider-apartments-in-rogers-park-amid-hot-chicago-weather-residents-call-for-action.html</guid><description>CHICAGO (WLS) — On Sunday night, the air conditioning was on at a North Side building. Finally, tenants said, there is relief inside their homes after last week’s heat spell. But now, some are enduring a different kind of restlessness.
“I was afraid to sleep,” said Lorna Barnes, a victim’s friend and a building resident.
Instead of enduring heat, tenants are enduring heartbreak and, they said, uncertainty in their own sanctuaries.</description></item><item><title>P2istheName Net Worth and Earnings</title><link>/p2isthename-net-worth-and-earnings.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/p2isthename-net-worth-and-earnings.html</guid><description>Date of BirthApril 23, 1998Age26 years oldBirthplaceUnited StatesP2istheName’s estimated net worth is $2 million. Read to know how we have calculated his net worth, earnings from YouTube, and other income sources.
Quick IntroP2istheName is an American YouTuber who is best-known for uploading NBA 2K PvP videos, montages, and Let’s Plays on his channel, P2istheName. P2istheName started the channel on May 16, 2011. Since then, he has earned more than 3.</description></item><item><title>Tony Dungy Health Update: What Happened To Him? Is He Sick?</title><link>/tony-dungy-illness.html</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/tony-dungy-illness.html</guid><description>"Despite being 68 years old, there are no signs of Tony Dungy Illness." He seems to be in good health, affluent, and smart." However, one of his boys
Read MorencG1vNJzZmiamaS0s63PobCgoaOpe6S7zGirmp9fqbyvxYydrKefqWK2rbjNnqqsZw%3D%3D</description></item><item><title>Jessica Ditzel: Unveiling the Enigmatic Figures Age, Height, Net Worth and Her Noteworthy Husband</title><link>/jessica-ditzel.html</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/jessica-ditzel.html</guid><description>Jessica Ditzel is an American television producer and former cocktail waitress.
She is better known as the spouse of the former MMA fighter Joe Rogan.
She was born on 18th July 1975 in Sugar Land, Texas.
Jessica was raised along with her sister Trinity Ditzel in Texas.
She went to Doherty High School.
Similarly, she attended California State University from where she earned a Bachelor’s degree.
How old is Jessica Ditzel?</description></item><item><title>13-time MLB All-Star ___ Griffey Jr.</title><link>/13-time-mlb-all-star-griffey-jr-html.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/13-time-mlb-all-star-griffey-jr-html.html</guid><description>Crosswords with Friends December 9 2019 13-time MLB All-Star ___ Griffey Jr. General knowledge plays a crucial role in solving crosswords, especially the 13-time MLB All-Star ___ Griffey Jr. crossword clue&amp;nbsp;which has appeared on December 9 2019 Crosswords with Friends&amp;nbsp;puzzle. The answer we have shared for 13-time MLB All-Star ___ Griffey Jr. has a total of 3 letters but also has other possible answers listed below the main one.</description></item><item><title>Eva Marcille Looked Gorgeous At Cynthia Baileys Wedding Check Out Her Hairdo!</title><link>/eva-marcille-looked-gorgeous-at-cynthia-baileys-wedding-check-out-her-hairdo-444924.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/eva-marcille-looked-gorgeous-at-cynthia-baileys-wedding-check-out-her-hairdo-444924.html</guid><description>Eva Marcille shared a photo on her social media account from her BFF, Cynthia Bailey’s wedding. She looked divine and managed to shock a lot of fans with her hairdo.
Fans freaked out that Eva wore white to the wedding, and some fans had something to say about her hair.
A follower said: ‘I don’t think you are supposed to wear white to someone’s wedding,’ and someone responded: ‘she’s in the wedding !</description></item><item><title>Is Kourtney Kardashian Engaged To Travis Barker?</title><link>/is-kourtney-kardashian-engaged-to-travis-barker-486395.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/is-kourtney-kardashian-engaged-to-travis-barker-486395.html</guid><description>Is Kourtney Kardashian engaged to her boyfriend Travis Barker? Though the couple hasn’t publicly announced wedding plans, speculation is at an all-time high that an engagement is coming soon. Kourtney’s love life heated up just as her sisters’ romances seem to be fizzling&amp;nbsp; First, Kim Kardashian filed for divorce from her husband of six years, Kanye West, and now Khloe Kardashian is dealing with new Tristan Thompson cheating allegations! Now, all eyes are on Kourtney and Travis to see what their next move will be.</description></item></channel></rss>